[
  {
    "idx": "0",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (11,6,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2  | P0\nD3 D4 D5  | P1\n---------\nP2 P3 P4   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 0 0 0\n0 0 1 1\n1 1 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 0, column 1. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "2",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "1",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (15,9,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2  | P0\nD3 D4 D5  | P1\nD6 D7 D8  | P2\n---------\nP3 P4 P5   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 0 1 0\n1 1 0 0\n1 1 0 0\n1 0 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "3",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "2",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (19,12,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3  | P0\nD4 D5 D6 D7  | P1\nD8 D9 D10 D11  | P2\n------------\nP3 P4 P5 P6   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 0 0 0 0\n0 0 0 1 1\n0 0 1 0 1\n0 0 1 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "3",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "3",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (15,9,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2  | P0\nD3 D4 D5  | P1\nD6 D7 D8  | P2\n---------\nP3 P4 P5   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 0 0 0\n0 0 1 1\n0 0 1 1\n0 0 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "3",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "4",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (11,6,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2  | P0\nD3 D4 D5  | P1\n---------\nP2 P3 P4   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 0 1 1\n0 0 0 1\n0 0 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 1, column 2. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "2",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "5",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (15,9,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2  | P0\nD3 D4 D5  | P1\nD6 D7 D8  | P2\n---------\nP3 P4 P5   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 0 0 1\n1 0 0 1\n1 0 1 0\n1 0 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "3",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "6",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (14,8,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3  | P0\nD4 D5 D6 D7  | P1\n------------\nP2 P3 P4 P5   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 0 1 1 0\n0 0 0 1 1\n0 0 1 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "2",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "7",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (15,9,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2  | P0\nD3 D4 D5  | P1\nD6 D7 D8  | P2\n---------\nP3 P4 P5   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 0 0 1\n0 0 1 1\n0 0 1 0\n1 0 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 2, column 2. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "3",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "8",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (15,9,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2  | P0\nD3 D4 D5  | P1\nD6 D7 D8  | P2\n---------\nP3 P4 P5   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 0 0 0\n0 0 1 1\n0 0 1 1\n0 0 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 0, column 0. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "3",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "9",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (15,9,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2  | P0\nD3 D4 D5  | P1\nD6 D7 D8  | P2\n---------\nP3 P4 P5   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 0 0 1\n1 1 0 0\n0 0 1 0\n1 1 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 2, column 0. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "3",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "10",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (24,16,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3  | P0\nD4 D5 D6 D7  | P1\nD8 D9 D10 D11  | P2\nD12 D13 D14 D15  | P3\n------------\nP4 P5 P6 P7   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 1 0 1 0\n0 0 0 0 0\n1 1 0 1 1\n0 1 0 1 1\n1 1 0 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 3, column 3. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "4",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "11",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (24,16,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3  | P0\nD4 D5 D6 D7  | P1\nD8 D9 D10 D11  | P2\nD12 D13 D14 D15  | P3\n------------\nP4 P5 P6 P7   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 0 0 0 0\n0 1 0 1 0\n0 0 0 1 1\n0 0 0 0 0\n0 1 0 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "4",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "12",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (19,12,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3  | P0\nD4 D5 D6 D7  | P1\nD8 D9 D10 D11  | P2\n------------\nP3 P4 P5 P6   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 1 1 0 1\n0 1 0 1 0\n1 0 0 0 0\n0 1 1 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 2, column 1. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "3",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "13",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (23,15,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4  | P0\nD5 D6 D7 D8 D9  | P1\nD10 D11 D12 D13 D14  | P2\n---------------\nP3 P4 P5 P6 P7   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 1 0 1 0 0\n0 1 1 0 1 1\n1 0 0 0 1 0\n1 0 1 1 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "3",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "14",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (23,15,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4  | P0\nD5 D6 D7 D8 D9  | P1\nD10 D11 D12 D13 D14  | P2\n---------------\nP3 P4 P5 P6 P7   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 0 1 0 1 0\n1 1 1 1 0 0\n0 0 0 0 1 0\n1 0 0 1 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 2, column 1. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "3",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "15",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (29,20,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4  | P0\nD5 D6 D7 D8 D9  | P1\nD10 D11 D12 D13 D14  | P2\nD15 D16 D17 D18 D19  | P3\n---------------\nP4 P5 P6 P7 P8   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 1 1 1 1 0\n1 0 0 1 0 0\n1 0 0 1 0 0\n1 0 0 1 0 0\n1 1 1 0 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "4",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "16",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (29,20,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4  | P0\nD5 D6 D7 D8 D9  | P1\nD10 D11 D12 D13 D14  | P2\nD15 D16 D17 D18 D19  | P3\n---------------\nP4 P5 P6 P7 P8   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 0 1 1 0 1\n1 0 1 1 1 0\n1 0 1 1 1 0\n1 1 1 0 0 1\n0 1 0 1 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "4",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "17",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (24,16,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3  | P0\nD4 D5 D6 D7  | P1\nD8 D9 D10 D11  | P2\nD12 D13 D14 D15  | P3\n------------\nP4 P5 P6 P7   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 0 1 1 1\n1 1 0 1 1\n0 1 0 0 1\n0 0 1 1 0\n0 0 0 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "4",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "18",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (19,12,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3  | P0\nD4 D5 D6 D7  | P1\nD8 D9 D10 D11  | P2\n------------\nP3 P4 P5 P6   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 1 1 1 0\n0 1 0 0 1\n0 1 1 0 1\n0 1 0 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 2, column 0. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "3",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "19",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (23,15,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4  | P0\nD5 D6 D7 D8 D9  | P1\nD10 D11 D12 D13 D14  | P2\n---------------\nP3 P4 P5 P6 P7   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 0 0 1 0 1\n1 1 0 1 1 1\n0 0 1 0 1 0\n1 1 1 1 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 1, column 3. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "3",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "20",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (29,20,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4  | P0\nD5 D6 D7 D8 D9  | P1\nD10 D11 D12 D13 D14  | P2\nD15 D16 D17 D18 D19  | P3\n---------------\nP4 P5 P6 P7 P8   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 1 1 1 0 1\n1 0 1 0 1 1\n0 0 1 0 1 0\n0 1 0 1 1 1\n1 0 1 0 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "4",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "21",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (41,30,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5  | P0\nD6 D7 D8 D9 D10 D11  | P1\nD12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17  | P2\nD18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23  | P3\nD24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29  | P4\n------------------\nP5 P6 P7 P8 P9 P10   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 0 1 1 1 0 0\n0 1 0 1 1 0 1\n0 1 1 1 1 1 1\n1 0 1 0 1 1 0\n0 1 1 1 1 1 1\n0 1 0 0 1 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "5",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "22",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (34,24,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5  | P0\nD6 D7 D8 D9 D10 D11  | P1\nD12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17  | P2\nD18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23  | P3\n------------------\nP4 P5 P6 P7 P8 P9   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 1 0 1 1 1 1\n0 1 0 0 1 0 0\n1 1 0 0 0 1 1\n0 0 0 1 0 0 1\n1 1 1 0 0 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 0, column 2. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "4",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "23",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (41,30,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5  | P0\nD6 D7 D8 D9 D10 D11  | P1\nD12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17  | P2\nD18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23  | P3\nD24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29  | P4\n------------------\nP5 P6 P7 P8 P9 P10   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 0 1 1 1 1 0\n0 1 1 1 1 1 1\n1 1 0 0 0 1 1\n1 0 0 0 1 1 1\n1 0 0 0 0 0 1\n0 0 0 0 0 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 0, column 4. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "5",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "24",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (29,20,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4  | P0\nD5 D6 D7 D8 D9  | P1\nD10 D11 D12 D13 D14  | P2\nD15 D16 D17 D18 D19  | P3\n---------------\nP4 P5 P6 P7 P8   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 1 1 0 1 1\n1 1 0 0 1 1\n1 1 0 1 1 0\n0 1 1 0 1 1\n1 0 0 0 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 0, column 3. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "4",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "25",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (29,20,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4  | P0\nD5 D6 D7 D8 D9  | P1\nD10 D11 D12 D13 D14  | P2\nD15 D16 D17 D18 D19  | P3\n---------------\nP4 P5 P6 P7 P8   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 0 0 1 0 0\n1 1 1 1 0 1\n1 1 1 0 1 0\n0 0 1 0 1 0\n1 1 1 0 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 1, column 1. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "4",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "26",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (34,24,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5  | P0\nD6 D7 D8 D9 D10 D11  | P1\nD12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17  | P2\nD18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23  | P3\n------------------\nP4 P5 P6 P7 P8 P9   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 1 1 0 0 0 0\n1 0 0 1 0 1 1\n1 0 0 1 0 0 0\n0 1 1 0 0 1 1\n0 0 0 0 0 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "4",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "27",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (29,20,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4  | P0\nD5 D6 D7 D8 D9  | P1\nD10 D11 D12 D13 D14  | P2\nD15 D16 D17 D18 D19  | P3\n---------------\nP4 P5 P6 P7 P8   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 1 0 0 1 0\n0 1 1 0 0 0\n1 1 0 1 1 0\n0 1 1 1 1 0\n1 0 0 0 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 0, column 0. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "4",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "28",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (29,20,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4  | P0\nD5 D6 D7 D8 D9  | P1\nD10 D11 D12 D13 D14  | P2\nD15 D16 D17 D18 D19  | P3\n---------------\nP4 P5 P6 P7 P8   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 0 0 1 1 0\n1 0 0 1 0 0\n0 0 0 0 0 0\n0 0 1 1 0 0\n0 0 1 1 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 0, column 4. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "4",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "29",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (41,30,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5  | P0\nD6 D7 D8 D9 D10 D11  | P1\nD12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17  | P2\nD18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23  | P3\nD24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29  | P4\n------------------\nP5 P6 P7 P8 P9 P10   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 0 1 1 1 0 1\n0 0 0 0 0 0 1\n1 1 0 0 1 1 0\n0 0 0 0 0 0 0\n1 0 0 1 1 1 0\n1 1 1 0 1 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 1, column 0. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "5",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "30",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (41,30,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5  | P0\nD6 D7 D8 D9 D10 D11  | P1\nD12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17  | P2\nD18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23  | P3\nD24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29  | P4\n------------------\nP5 P6 P7 P8 P9 P10   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 0 1 1 1 1 1\n0 0 1 0 1 1 0\n1 0 1 0 0 0 0\n1 0 1 1 0 1 0\n1 1 0 1 1 1 1\n0 0 0 1 1 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 1, column 1. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "5",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "31",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (48,36,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5  | P0\nD6 D7 D8 D9 D10 D11  | P1\nD12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17  | P2\nD18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23  | P3\nD24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29  | P4\nD30 D31 D32 D33 D34 D35  | P5\n------------------\nP6 P7 P8 P9 P10 P11   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 1 0 1 1 0 1\n0 1 1 1 0 1 0\n0 1 0 0 0 1 0\n0 0 0 1 1 1 1\n0 1 0 1 0 0 0\n1 1 1 1 0 0 0\n1 1 0 1 0 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "6",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "32",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (55,42,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6  | P0\nD7 D8 D9 D10 D11 D12 D13  | P1\nD14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19 D20  | P2\nD21 D22 D23 D24 D25 D26 D27  | P3\nD28 D29 D30 D31 D32 D33 D34  | P4\nD35 D36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41  | P5\n---------------------\nP6 P7 P8 P9 P10 P11 P12   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 0 1 0 1 1 1 0\n1 0 0 1 0 1 0 1\n0 1 1 0 1 0 1 0\n1 0 0 1 0 1 0 1\n0 0 0 0 1 1 1 1\n0 1 0 0 0 0 1 0\n1 1 0 0 1 0 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 0, column 1. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "6",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "33",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (48,36,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5  | P0\nD6 D7 D8 D9 D10 D11  | P1\nD12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17  | P2\nD18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23  | P3\nD24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29  | P4\nD30 D31 D32 D33 D34 D35  | P5\n------------------\nP6 P7 P8 P9 P10 P11   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 0 0 1 1 0 0\n1 1 1 1 1 0 0\n1 1 0 1 0 1 0\n1 1 1 0 1 0 0\n0 1 0 1 1 1 0\n0 1 1 0 1 1 0\n1 0 1 0 1 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 1, column 1. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "6",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "34",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (41,30,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5  | P0\nD6 D7 D8 D9 D10 D11  | P1\nD12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17  | P2\nD18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23  | P3\nD24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29  | P4\n------------------\nP5 P6 P7 P8 P9 P10   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 1 1 0 0 0 1\n0 1 0 0 1 1 1\n1 0 0 1 1 0 1\n1 0 1 1 0 1 0\n0 0 1 1 0 0 0\n1 0 1 1 0 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "5",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "35",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (47,35,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6  | P0\nD7 D8 D9 D10 D11 D12 D13  | P1\nD14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19 D20  | P2\nD21 D22 D23 D24 D25 D26 D27  | P3\nD28 D29 D30 D31 D32 D33 D34  | P4\n---------------------\nP5 P6 P7 P8 P9 P10 P11   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 0 1 0 1 1 0 0\n0 0 1 1 0 1 0 1\n1 1 1 1 1 0 0 1\n0 1 0 1 0 1 1 0\n1 0 0 1 0 1 0 1\n1 0 1 0 0 0 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "5",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "36",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (55,42,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6  | P0\nD7 D8 D9 D10 D11 D12 D13  | P1\nD14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19 D20  | P2\nD21 D22 D23 D24 D25 D26 D27  | P3\nD28 D29 D30 D31 D32 D33 D34  | P4\nD35 D36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41  | P5\n---------------------\nP6 P7 P8 P9 P10 P11 P12   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 1 0 0 0 0 1 1\n1 0 0 0 0 0 1 0\n1 0 0 1 1 0 1 0\n0 1 1 1 1 1 0 1\n1 1 0 0 1 0 1 0\n1 1 1 0 1 1 0 1\n1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "6",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "37",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (55,42,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6  | P0\nD7 D8 D9 D10 D11 D12 D13  | P1\nD14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19 D20  | P2\nD21 D22 D23 D24 D25 D26 D27  | P3\nD28 D29 D30 D31 D32 D33 D34  | P4\nD35 D36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41  | P5\n---------------------\nP6 P7 P8 P9 P10 P11 P12   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 0 0 1 0 1 0 1\n0 0 0 1 0 1 1 1\n1 1 0 1 1 0 1 1\n1 1 0 0 0 1 0 1\n0 1 1 1 1 1 1 0\n1 1 1 0 0 0 1 0\n0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "6",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "38",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (55,42,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6  | P0\nD7 D8 D9 D10 D11 D12 D13  | P1\nD14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19 D20  | P2\nD21 D22 D23 D24 D25 D26 D27  | P3\nD28 D29 D30 D31 D32 D33 D34  | P4\nD35 D36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41  | P5\n---------------------\nP6 P7 P8 P9 P10 P11 P12   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 0 1 1 0 0 1 0\n0 1 0 0 0 0 1 1\n1 1 1 0 0 1 0 0\n1 1 1 1 0 1 1 0\n0 1 0 1 0 0 1 1\n1 0 0 1 1 0 1 0\n0 0 0 0 1 0 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 1, column 2. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "6",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "39",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (55,42,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6  | P0\nD7 D8 D9 D10 D11 D12 D13  | P1\nD14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19 D20  | P2\nD21 D22 D23 D24 D25 D26 D27  | P3\nD28 D29 D30 D31 D32 D33 D34  | P4\nD35 D36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41  | P5\n---------------------\nP6 P7 P8 P9 P10 P11 P12   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 0 0 1 0 1 1 0\n1 0 0 1 1 1 0 0\n0 0 0 1 0 1 0 0\n1 0 1 0 1 1 0 0\n0 1 0 1 1 0 0 1\n1 0 0 1 0 0 0 0\n0 1 1 1 1 0 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "6",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "40",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (62,48,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7  | P0\nD8 D9 D10 D11 D12 D13 D14 D15  | P1\nD16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23  | P2\nD24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31  | P3\nD32 D33 D34 D35 D36 D37 D38 D39  | P4\nD40 D41 D42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47  | P5\n------------------------\nP6 P7 P8 P9 P10 P11 P12 P13   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 1 1 0 1 1 1 1 1\n0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 1\n0 1 1 1 1 1 0 0 0\n0 1 0 0 1 0 0 1 1\n1 1 1 1 0 1 0 1 0\n1 1 0 1 1 1 1 0 0\n1 1 1 0 0 0 1 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 2, column 6. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "6",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "41",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (62,48,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7  | P0\nD8 D9 D10 D11 D12 D13 D14 D15  | P1\nD16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23  | P2\nD24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31  | P3\nD32 D33 D34 D35 D36 D37 D38 D39  | P4\nD40 D41 D42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47  | P5\n------------------------\nP6 P7 P8 P9 P10 P11 P12 P13   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 1 1 0 1 1 0 0 0\n0 1 1 1 1 1 0 1 0\n1 1 1 0 1 0 1 1 0\n1 0 1 1 1 1 0 1 0\n1 0 1 1 1 0 0 1 1\n0 0 1 1 1 0 1 1 1\n1 1 0 0 0 1 0 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "6",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "42",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (71,56,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7  | P0\nD8 D9 D10 D11 D12 D13 D14 D15  | P1\nD16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23  | P2\nD24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31  | P3\nD32 D33 D34 D35 D36 D37 D38 D39  | P4\nD40 D41 D42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47  | P5\nD48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53 D54 D55  | P6\n------------------------\nP7 P8 P9 P10 P11 P12 P13 P14   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 0 0 1 1 1 0 0 0\n0 1 0 1 1 1 0 0 0\n1 1 0 0 1 1 1 1 0\n0 1 0 1 1 0 0 0 1\n0 1 0 1 0 0 0 1 1\n1 0 1 1 0 1 0 1 1\n1 0 1 0 1 1 0 1 0\n0 0 1 1 1 1 1 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 6, column 2. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "7",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "43",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (63,49,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6  | P0\nD7 D8 D9 D10 D11 D12 D13  | P1\nD14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19 D20  | P2\nD21 D22 D23 D24 D25 D26 D27  | P3\nD28 D29 D30 D31 D32 D33 D34  | P4\nD35 D36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41  | P5\nD42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47 D48  | P6\n---------------------\nP7 P8 P9 P10 P11 P12 P13   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 1 1 0 0 0 1 0\n1 0 0 1 1 1 1 1\n1 1 0 0 0 1 0 0\n0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0\n0 0 1 1 1 0 0 1\n1 1 1 0 1 1 0 1\n0 1 0 1 0 0 1 1\n1 0 1 1 1 1 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 2, column 0. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "7",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "44",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (71,56,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7  | P0\nD8 D9 D10 D11 D12 D13 D14 D15  | P1\nD16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23  | P2\nD24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31  | P3\nD32 D33 D34 D35 D36 D37 D38 D39  | P4\nD40 D41 D42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47  | P5\nD48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53 D54 D55  | P6\n------------------------\nP7 P8 P9 P10 P11 P12 P13 P14   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 1 0 1 1 1 1 1 0\n0 0 1 1 0 0 0 0 0\n0 1 0 1 0 1 1 0 0\n0 0 0 0 1 1 0 1 1\n1 1 0 0 0 1 0 0 1\n1 0 0 1 0 1 0 1 0\n1 1 0 0 0 1 1 1 1\n1 0 1 0 0 0 1 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "7",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "45",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (55,42,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6  | P0\nD7 D8 D9 D10 D11 D12 D13  | P1\nD14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19 D20  | P2\nD21 D22 D23 D24 D25 D26 D27  | P3\nD28 D29 D30 D31 D32 D33 D34  | P4\nD35 D36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41  | P5\n---------------------\nP6 P7 P8 P9 P10 P11 P12   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 1 0 1 0 1 1 1\n0 1 1 0 1 0 0 1\n1 1 0 0 1 1 0 1\n1 1 1 1 0 0 1 1\n1 0 0 1 1 0 1 0\n1 1 1 1 0 0 0 0\n0 1 1 0 1 0 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 2, column 0. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "6",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "46",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (71,56,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7  | P0\nD8 D9 D10 D11 D12 D13 D14 D15  | P1\nD16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23  | P2\nD24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31  | P3\nD32 D33 D34 D35 D36 D37 D38 D39  | P4\nD40 D41 D42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47  | P5\nD48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53 D54 D55  | P6\n------------------------\nP7 P8 P9 P10 P11 P12 P13 P14   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 1 1 0 0 1 1 1 1\n0 1 1 1 0 0 0 1 0\n0 0 1 0 0 1 1 0 1\n0 1 1 1 1 0 1 1 0\n1 0 1 0 1 0 0 0 1\n1 1 0 1 0 0 0 0 1\n1 0 0 1 1 1 1 1 0\n0 0 1 1 1 1 0 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 0, column 3. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "7",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "47",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (62,48,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7  | P0\nD8 D9 D10 D11 D12 D13 D14 D15  | P1\nD16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23  | P2\nD24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31  | P3\nD32 D33 D34 D35 D36 D37 D38 D39  | P4\nD40 D41 D42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47  | P5\n------------------------\nP6 P7 P8 P9 P10 P11 P12 P13   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 0 0 1 1 0 0 0 0\n0 1 1 0 0 0 0 1 1\n0 0 1 1 1 1 1 1 0\n1 0 0 0 0 1 1 0 1\n1 0 1 0 0 1 1 0 0\n0 1 0 1 0 1 0 0 1\n0 0 1 1 0 0 1 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "6",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "48",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (55,42,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6  | P0\nD7 D8 D9 D10 D11 D12 D13  | P1\nD14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19 D20  | P2\nD21 D22 D23 D24 D25 D26 D27  | P3\nD28 D29 D30 D31 D32 D33 D34  | P4\nD35 D36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41  | P5\n---------------------\nP6 P7 P8 P9 P10 P11 P12   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 1 1 0 0 0 0 0\n0 1 0 1 1 0 0 1\n0 1 0 1 0 1 0 1\n0 1 1 0 0 0 1 1\n1 0 0 0 0 1 1 1\n0 1 0 1 0 0 1 1\n1 1 0 1 1 0 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "6",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "49",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (63,49,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6  | P0\nD7 D8 D9 D10 D11 D12 D13  | P1\nD14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19 D20  | P2\nD21 D22 D23 D24 D25 D26 D27  | P3\nD28 D29 D30 D31 D32 D33 D34  | P4\nD35 D36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41  | P5\nD42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47 D48  | P6\n---------------------\nP7 P8 P9 P10 P11 P12 P13   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 1 0 0 0 1 0 1\n1 0 0 0 0 0 1 0\n1 1 0 0 1 0 0 1\n0 0 1 0 0 1 1 1\n1 0 0 1 1 0 0 1\n0 0 0 1 1 1 1 0\n1 0 1 0 1 1 0 0\n1 0 0 0 0 0 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "7",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "50",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (71,56,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7  | P0\nD8 D9 D10 D11 D12 D13 D14 D15  | P1\nD16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23  | P2\nD24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31  | P3\nD32 D33 D34 D35 D36 D37 D38 D39  | P4\nD40 D41 D42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47  | P5\nD48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53 D54 D55  | P6\n------------------------\nP7 P8 P9 P10 P11 P12 P13 P14   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 1 1 0 1 1 1 1 1\n1 0 1 1 1 0 0 0 0\n1 0 0 0 1 1 0 1 0\n1 1 0 0 0 0 1 1 0\n0 1 1 0 1 0 0 1 0\n0 0 0 1 1 1 1 1 1\n0 1 0 1 1 1 0 0 0\n0 0 1 1 0 0 1 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "7",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "51",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (71,56,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7  | P0\nD8 D9 D10 D11 D12 D13 D14 D15  | P1\nD16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23  | P2\nD24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31  | P3\nD32 D33 D34 D35 D36 D37 D38 D39  | P4\nD40 D41 D42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47  | P5\nD48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53 D54 D55  | P6\n------------------------\nP7 P8 P9 P10 P11 P12 P13 P14   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 1 1 1 0 1 0 0 0\n1 0 0 1 0 1 1 0 0\n1 1 0 1 0 0 1 1 1\n1 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0\n1 1 1 1 0 0 0 1 1\n0 0 0 1 0 1 1 1 1\n0 1 1 1 1 1 0 0 1\n0 1 1 1 1 0 1 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 5, column 3. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "7",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "52",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (71,56,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7  | P0\nD8 D9 D10 D11 D12 D13 D14 D15  | P1\nD16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23  | P2\nD24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31  | P3\nD32 D33 D34 D35 D36 D37 D38 D39  | P4\nD40 D41 D42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47  | P5\nD48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53 D54 D55  | P6\n------------------------\nP7 P8 P9 P10 P11 P12 P13 P14   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0\n1 0 1 0 1 0 1 0 0\n1 1 1 1 0 1 1 0 1\n0 0 1 0 0 1 0 1 1\n0 1 0 0 1 1 0 0 1\n1 1 1 0 0 0 0 0 1\n0 1 0 0 0 1 0 1 1\n0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 2, column 1. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "7",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "53",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (71,56,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7  | P0\nD8 D9 D10 D11 D12 D13 D14 D15  | P1\nD16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23  | P2\nD24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31  | P3\nD32 D33 D34 D35 D36 D37 D38 D39  | P4\nD40 D41 D42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47  | P5\nD48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53 D54 D55  | P6\n------------------------\nP7 P8 P9 P10 P11 P12 P13 P14   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 1 1 0 1 0 1 0 0\n0 0 1 1 0 1 1 1 1\n0 1 1 1 0 0 0 0 1\n0 1 0 1 1 1 0 0 1\n1 0 0 1 0 1 0 1 0\n0 1 0 0 0 0 1 1 1\n1 1 1 1 1 1 1 1 0\n0 1 0 1 1 0 1 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 3, column 6. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "7",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "54",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (79,63,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8  | P0\nD9 D10 D11 D12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17  | P1\nD18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23 D24 D25 D26  | P2\nD27 D28 D29 D30 D31 D32 D33 D34 D35  | P3\nD36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41 D42 D43 D44  | P4\nD45 D46 D47 D48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53  | P5\nD54 D55 D56 D57 D58 D59 D60 D61 D62  | P6\n---------------------------\nP7 P8 P9 P10 P11 P12 P13 P14 P15   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 0 1 0 0 1 1 1 1 1\n0 0 1 1 1 1 0 0 1 1\n0 1 1 1 0 0 0 0 1 0\n1 1 1 0 1 0 0 1 1 0\n1 1 0 0 1 0 1 1 0 0\n0 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 1\n1 0 1 0 0 1 0 1 0 0\n1 1 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 4, column 2. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "7",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "55",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (80,64,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7  | P0\nD8 D9 D10 D11 D12 D13 D14 D15  | P1\nD16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23  | P2\nD24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31  | P3\nD32 D33 D34 D35 D36 D37 D38 D39  | P4\nD40 D41 D42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47  | P5\nD48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53 D54 D55  | P6\nD56 D57 D58 D59 D60 D61 D62 D63  | P7\n------------------------\nP8 P9 P10 P11 P12 P13 P14 P15   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 1 1 0 0 0 1 0 0\n0 0 0 0 1 1 1 1 0\n1 1 1 1 0 1 1 1 0\n1 1 1 1 0 1 0 0 1\n0 0 1 1 0 1 0 1 0\n0 1 1 0 1 1 0 0 0\n0 0 0 1 0 0 0 1 0\n0 1 1 1 1 1 1 0 0\n1 1 0 1 1 0 1 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 2, column 6. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "8",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "56",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (79,63,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8  | P0\nD9 D10 D11 D12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17  | P1\nD18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23 D24 D25 D26  | P2\nD27 D28 D29 D30 D31 D32 D33 D34 D35  | P3\nD36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41 D42 D43 D44  | P4\nD45 D46 D47 D48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53  | P5\nD54 D55 D56 D57 D58 D59 D60 D61 D62  | P6\n---------------------------\nP7 P8 P9 P10 P11 P12 P13 P14 P15   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 0 0 1 1 1 1 1 0 1\n1 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 0 0\n0 0 0 0 1 0 1 1 1 0\n0 0 1 1 1 0 0 1 1 0\n1 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 1 1\n1 1 1 1 0 0 1 0 0 1\n1 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0\n0 0 1 1 0 1 1 0 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 3, column 1. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "7",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "57",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (89,72,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8  | P0\nD9 D10 D11 D12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17  | P1\nD18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23 D24 D25 D26  | P2\nD27 D28 D29 D30 D31 D32 D33 D34 D35  | P3\nD36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41 D42 D43 D44  | P4\nD45 D46 D47 D48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53  | P5\nD54 D55 D56 D57 D58 D59 D60 D61 D62  | P6\nD63 D64 D65 D66 D67 D68 D69 D70 D71  | P7\n---------------------------\nP8 P9 P10 P11 P12 P13 P14 P15 P16   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 0 0 1 0 1 0 0 1 0\n1 1 1 0 0 1 1 0 1 0\n0 0 1 0 1 1 1 1 1 0\n0 1 1 0 1 0 1 0 1 1\n0 0 0 1 0 1 1 0 0 0\n0 0 1 0 0 1 0 0 0 0\n1 1 1 0 1 0 1 0 0 1\n0 1 1 0 1 1 0 0 1 1\n1 0 0 1 0 0 1 1 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 4, column 3. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "8",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "58",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (71,56,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7  | P0\nD8 D9 D10 D11 D12 D13 D14 D15  | P1\nD16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23  | P2\nD24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31  | P3\nD32 D33 D34 D35 D36 D37 D38 D39  | P4\nD40 D41 D42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47  | P5\nD48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53 D54 D55  | P6\n------------------------\nP7 P8 P9 P10 P11 P12 P13 P14   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 0 1 0 1 1 1 1 1\n0 1 0 0 1 0 1 1 0\n1 1 0 0 1 0 0 0 1\n1 0 1 0 0 0 1 1 0\n1 1 0 1 1 0 0 1 1\n0 0 1 1 0 1 0 1 0\n1 1 0 1 1 1 1 0 0\n0 0 1 1 1 1 0 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "7",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "59",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (80,64,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7  | P0\nD8 D9 D10 D11 D12 D13 D14 D15  | P1\nD16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23  | P2\nD24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31  | P3\nD32 D33 D34 D35 D36 D37 D38 D39  | P4\nD40 D41 D42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47  | P5\nD48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53 D54 D55  | P6\nD56 D57 D58 D59 D60 D61 D62 D63  | P7\n------------------------\nP8 P9 P10 P11 P12 P13 P14 P15   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 1 1 1 1 1 1 1 1\n1 0 1 1 1 0 1 0 1\n1 0 1 1 1 1 0 1 1\n0 1 0 0 0 1 0 1 1\n0 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 1\n0 0 1 0 0 0 1 0 0\n1 0 0 1 1 0 1 0 0\n0 1 1 0 1 1 0 1 1\n1 0 1 0 1 0 0 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 2, column 1. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "8",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "60",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (99,81,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8  | P0\nD9 D10 D11 D12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17  | P1\nD18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23 D24 D25 D26  | P2\nD27 D28 D29 D30 D31 D32 D33 D34 D35  | P3\nD36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41 D42 D43 D44  | P4\nD45 D46 D47 D48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53  | P5\nD54 D55 D56 D57 D58 D59 D60 D61 D62  | P6\nD63 D64 D65 D66 D67 D68 D69 D70 D71  | P7\nD72 D73 D74 D75 D76 D77 D78 D79 D80  | P8\n---------------------------\nP9 P10 P11 P12 P13 P14 P15 P16 P17   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 1\n0 0 1 0 0 1 0 1 1 0\n0 0 0 1 0 0 1 1 0 1\n0 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 1\n1 0 1 1 0 1 1 1 1 1\n1 1 0 1 0 1 1 1 1 1\n0 1 1 0 0 1 0 1 0 0\n1 1 0 0 0 1 1 0 0 0\n0 1 0 1 0 1 0 1 1 1\n1 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 0, column 0. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "9",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "61",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (89,72,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8  | P0\nD9 D10 D11 D12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17  | P1\nD18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23 D24 D25 D26  | P2\nD27 D28 D29 D30 D31 D32 D33 D34 D35  | P3\nD36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41 D42 D43 D44  | P4\nD45 D46 D47 D48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53  | P5\nD54 D55 D56 D57 D58 D59 D60 D61 D62  | P6\nD63 D64 D65 D66 D67 D68 D69 D70 D71  | P7\n---------------------------\nP8 P9 P10 P11 P12 P13 P14 P15 P16   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 0 0 1 1 1 0 1 1 0\n1 0 0 1 1 0 1 1 0 1\n0 1 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0\n1 1 0 0 0 1 1 1 0 1\n1 0 1 0 1 1 1 1 0 0\n0 1 1 0 0 1 1 0 0 0\n1 0 0 1 1 0 0 0 1 0\n0 1 1 0 1 0 1 1 0 1\n0 0 1 1 1 0 1 1 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 0, column 3. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "8",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "62",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (98,80,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8 D9  | P0\nD10 D11 D12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19  | P1\nD20 D21 D22 D23 D24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29  | P2\nD30 D31 D32 D33 D34 D35 D36 D37 D38 D39  | P3\nD40 D41 D42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47 D48 D49  | P4\nD50 D51 D52 D53 D54 D55 D56 D57 D58 D59  | P5\nD60 D61 D62 D63 D64 D65 D66 D67 D68 D69  | P6\nD70 D71 D72 D73 D74 D75 D76 D77 D78 D79  | P7\n------------------------------\nP8 P9 P10 P11 P12 P13 P14 P15 P16 P17   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 1 1 1 0 0 0 1 0 0 1\n1 1 1 1 0 1 1 0 0 0 0\n1 0 1 0 0 1 1 1 1 0 0\n0 0 0 0 1 0 0 1 0 0 0\n0 1 0 1 0 0 0 0 1 0 1\n1 0 1 1 1 1 0 1 0 0 0\n1 1 1 0 1 0 1 0 0 0 1\n0 1 1 1 1 0 1 0 1 0 0\n1 1 0 1 0 1 0 0 1 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "8",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "63",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (109,90,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8 D9  | P0\nD10 D11 D12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19  | P1\nD20 D21 D22 D23 D24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29  | P2\nD30 D31 D32 D33 D34 D35 D36 D37 D38 D39  | P3\nD40 D41 D42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47 D48 D49  | P4\nD50 D51 D52 D53 D54 D55 D56 D57 D58 D59  | P5\nD60 D61 D62 D63 D64 D65 D66 D67 D68 D69  | P6\nD70 D71 D72 D73 D74 D75 D76 D77 D78 D79  | P7\nD80 D81 D82 D83 D84 D85 D86 D87 D88 D89  | P8\n------------------------------\nP9 P10 P11 P12 P13 P14 P15 P16 P17 P18   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 1 0 1 1 1 1 0 1 1 1\n1 0 0 0 0 1 1 0 0 1 1\n0 0 1 0 1 1 0 0 0 1 0\n0 1 0 1 1 1 1 1 1 0 1\n0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 1 0\n1 0 0 1 1 0 0 0 0 1 0\n0 0 1 1 0 1 0 1 0 0 0\n1 0 0 1 1 0 0 1 0 0 0\n0 0 0 1 0 1 0 0 0 1 1\n1 0 1 0 1 0 1 1 1 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 1, column 2. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "9",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "64",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (109,90,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8 D9  | P0\nD10 D11 D12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19  | P1\nD20 D21 D22 D23 D24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29  | P2\nD30 D31 D32 D33 D34 D35 D36 D37 D38 D39  | P3\nD40 D41 D42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47 D48 D49  | P4\nD50 D51 D52 D53 D54 D55 D56 D57 D58 D59  | P5\nD60 D61 D62 D63 D64 D65 D66 D67 D68 D69  | P6\nD70 D71 D72 D73 D74 D75 D76 D77 D78 D79  | P7\nD80 D81 D82 D83 D84 D85 D86 D87 D88 D89  | P8\n------------------------------\nP9 P10 P11 P12 P13 P14 P15 P16 P17 P18   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 0 1 1 0 1 0 1 1 0 1\n1 1 1 0 0 0 0 0 1 0 1\n0 1 0 1 1 0 0 0 1 1 1\n0 1 1 1 1 1 1 0 1 0 1\n1 0 0 0 1 1 1 1 1 0 0\n0 1 1 1 0 0 1 0 1 0 1\n0 0 1 1 1 0 0 1 1 0 1\n1 0 1 1 1 1 1 1 0 0 1\n0 0 1 1 1 0 0 0 0 1 0\n1 0 1 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 1, column 8. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "9",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "65",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (98,80,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8 D9  | P0\nD10 D11 D12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19  | P1\nD20 D21 D22 D23 D24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29  | P2\nD30 D31 D32 D33 D34 D35 D36 D37 D38 D39  | P3\nD40 D41 D42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47 D48 D49  | P4\nD50 D51 D52 D53 D54 D55 D56 D57 D58 D59  | P5\nD60 D61 D62 D63 D64 D65 D66 D67 D68 D69  | P6\nD70 D71 D72 D73 D74 D75 D76 D77 D78 D79  | P7\n------------------------------\nP8 P9 P10 P11 P12 P13 P14 P15 P16 P17   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 1 1 0 1 0 0 0 1 0 0\n1 1 0 0 1 0 1 1 0 1 0\n1 1 1 1 0 1 0 0 1 0 0\n0 1 0 1 1 1 1 1 0 0 1\n1 1 0 0 0 1 0 0 1 0 0\n0 1 1 1 0 0 1 1 0 0 1\n1 1 1 0 0 0 1 1 1 0 0\n1 0 0 0 1 0 1 0 0 1 0\n0 1 0 1 0 1 1 0 0 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 3, column 0. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "8",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "66",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (89,72,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8  | P0\nD9 D10 D11 D12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17  | P1\nD18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23 D24 D25 D26  | P2\nD27 D28 D29 D30 D31 D32 D33 D34 D35  | P3\nD36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41 D42 D43 D44  | P4\nD45 D46 D47 D48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53  | P5\nD54 D55 D56 D57 D58 D59 D60 D61 D62  | P6\nD63 D64 D65 D66 D67 D68 D69 D70 D71  | P7\n---------------------------\nP8 P9 P10 P11 P12 P13 P14 P15 P16   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 0 0 1 0 0 0 1 0 0\n0 0 1 1 1 1 0 0 1 1\n0 0 0 1 0 1 0 1 0 1\n1 0 1 0 1 1 0 0 0 0\n1 0 1 0 1 1 1 1 1 1\n1 0 0 0 0 1 1 1 0 0\n0 1 1 1 0 1 1 1 1 1\n1 1 1 0 1 1 0 0 1 0\n0 0 1 0 0 1 1 1 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "8",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "67",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (99,81,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8  | P0\nD9 D10 D11 D12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17  | P1\nD18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23 D24 D25 D26  | P2\nD27 D28 D29 D30 D31 D32 D33 D34 D35  | P3\nD36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41 D42 D43 D44  | P4\nD45 D46 D47 D48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53  | P5\nD54 D55 D56 D57 D58 D59 D60 D61 D62  | P6\nD63 D64 D65 D66 D67 D68 D69 D70 D71  | P7\nD72 D73 D74 D75 D76 D77 D78 D79 D80  | P8\n---------------------------\nP9 P10 P11 P12 P13 P14 P15 P16 P17   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 1 0 1 0 1 0 1 0 1\n0 1 1 0 0 1 0 1 1 1\n0 1 1 0 0 1 0 1 0 0\n0 0 1 1 1 1 1 0 1 0\n0 0 1 0 0 1 0 0 0 0\n0 0 1 0 1 1 1 0 0 0\n0 1 1 1 1 1 1 1 1 1\n1 1 1 1 1 0 0 1 1 1\n1 0 0 1 1 0 0 1 0 0\n1 1 1 1 1 1 0 0 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 6, column 6. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "9",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "68",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (89,72,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8  | P0\nD9 D10 D11 D12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17  | P1\nD18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23 D24 D25 D26  | P2\nD27 D28 D29 D30 D31 D32 D33 D34 D35  | P3\nD36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41 D42 D43 D44  | P4\nD45 D46 D47 D48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53  | P5\nD54 D55 D56 D57 D58 D59 D60 D61 D62  | P6\nD63 D64 D65 D66 D67 D68 D69 D70 D71  | P7\n---------------------------\nP8 P9 P10 P11 P12 P13 P14 P15 P16   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 1 0 1 0 0 1 0 1 1\n0 0 1 1 1 0 0 1 1 1\n0 1 1 1 1 0 0 0 1 1\n0 1 1 0 1 0 1 1 1 0\n1 0 0 1 0 0 1 0 0 1\n1 1 0 1 0 1 1 1 1 0\n1 0 1 0 0 1 1 0 1 1\n0 1 1 1 0 1 0 0 1 1\n0 1 0 0 1 1 1 1 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 5, column 2. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "8",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "69",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (99,81,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8  | P0\nD9 D10 D11 D12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17  | P1\nD18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23 D24 D25 D26  | P2\nD27 D28 D29 D30 D31 D32 D33 D34 D35  | P3\nD36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41 D42 D43 D44  | P4\nD45 D46 D47 D48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53  | P5\nD54 D55 D56 D57 D58 D59 D60 D61 D62  | P6\nD63 D64 D65 D66 D67 D68 D69 D70 D71  | P7\nD72 D73 D74 D75 D76 D77 D78 D79 D80  | P8\n---------------------------\nP9 P10 P11 P12 P13 P14 P15 P16 P17   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 1 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 1\n0 0 1 1 0 1 0 0 0 1\n0 1 1 0 0 0 1 1 1 1\n1 1 1 0 0 1 1 1 0 0\n0 1 1 0 1 1 0 0 0 0\n1 1 0 1 0 0 0 1 1 1\n1 0 0 1 0 1 1 0 1 1\n0 1 1 0 1 0 1 1 0 1\n0 1 0 0 0 0 1 1 1 1\n0 1 1 0 0 1 1 1 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 8, column 3. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "9",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "70",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (131,110,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8 D9 D10  | P0\nD11 D12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21  | P1\nD22 D23 D24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31 D32  | P2\nD33 D34 D35 D36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41 D42 D43  | P3\nD44 D45 D46 D47 D48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53 D54  | P4\nD55 D56 D57 D58 D59 D60 D61 D62 D63 D64 D65  | P5\nD66 D67 D68 D69 D70 D71 D72 D73 D74 D75 D76  | P6\nD77 D78 D79 D80 D81 D82 D83 D84 D85 D86 D87  | P7\nD88 D89 D90 D91 D92 D93 D94 D95 D96 D97 D98  | P8\nD99 D100 D101 D102 D103 D104 D105 D106 D107 D108 D109  | P9\n---------------------------------\nP10 P11 P12 P13 P14 P15 P16 P17 P18 P19 P20   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 0 1 0 1 0 0 1 0 0 0 1\n0 0 0 1 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0\n1 0 1 1 0 1 0 0 1 1 1 1\n1 0 1 1 0 1 0 0 1 0 1 0\n1 1 1 1 0 0 1 0 1 1 1 0\n0 0 1 1 0 0 0 0 1 0 1 0\n0 1 1 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 1\n0 0 1 1 0 0 0 1 0 1 1 1\n1 0 0 1 0 1 1 1 0 1 0 0\n1 1 0 0 1 1 0 0 1 0 0 1\n1 1 1 0 0 0 0 0 1 0 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "10",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "71",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (131,110,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8 D9 D10  | P0\nD11 D12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21  | P1\nD22 D23 D24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31 D32  | P2\nD33 D34 D35 D36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41 D42 D43  | P3\nD44 D45 D46 D47 D48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53 D54  | P4\nD55 D56 D57 D58 D59 D60 D61 D62 D63 D64 D65  | P5\nD66 D67 D68 D69 D70 D71 D72 D73 D74 D75 D76  | P6\nD77 D78 D79 D80 D81 D82 D83 D84 D85 D86 D87  | P7\nD88 D89 D90 D91 D92 D93 D94 D95 D96 D97 D98  | P8\nD99 D100 D101 D102 D103 D104 D105 D106 D107 D108 D109  | P9\n---------------------------------\nP10 P11 P12 P13 P14 P15 P16 P17 P18 P19 P20   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 1 1 0 1 1 0 0 0 0 1 0\n0 0 0 1 1 0 0 1 0 1 0 0\n0 0 1 1 1 0 1 0 0 0 1 1\n0 0 1 1 1 0 1 1 1 1 0 1\n0 0 0 1 1 1 1 0 0 1 1 0\n0 1 0 1 1 0 1 0 0 1 0 1\n1 1 0 0 0 0 1 1 0 0 1 1\n1 1 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 1 0\n0 0 0 0 1 0 0 1 0 0 0 0\n0 0 0 0 1 0 1 0 0 0 0 0\n1 0 1 1 0 1 0 0 1 0 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "10",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "72",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (131,110,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8 D9 D10  | P0\nD11 D12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21  | P1\nD22 D23 D24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31 D32  | P2\nD33 D34 D35 D36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41 D42 D43  | P3\nD44 D45 D46 D47 D48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53 D54  | P4\nD55 D56 D57 D58 D59 D60 D61 D62 D63 D64 D65  | P5\nD66 D67 D68 D69 D70 D71 D72 D73 D74 D75 D76  | P6\nD77 D78 D79 D80 D81 D82 D83 D84 D85 D86 D87  | P7\nD88 D89 D90 D91 D92 D93 D94 D95 D96 D97 D98  | P8\nD99 D100 D101 D102 D103 D104 D105 D106 D107 D108 D109  | P9\n---------------------------------\nP10 P11 P12 P13 P14 P15 P16 P17 P18 P19 P20   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 1 1 0 0 1 0 0 1 1 1 0\n0 1 0 1 0 0 1 1 1 1 1 1\n1 0 0 1 0 1 0 0 1 0 1 1\n0 1 0 0 0 1 0 1 0 1 1 1\n1 0 1 0 1 1 1 1 0 1 1 0\n0 0 1 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 1\n1 1 0 0 0 0 1 1 0 1 0 1\n1 0 1 1 1 1 1 0 1 0 1 0\n0 1 0 1 1 1 0 0 0 1 0 1\n0 1 1 0 1 1 0 1 0 1 1 1\n0 0 1 0 0 1 0 0 0 1 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 5, column 10. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "10",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "73",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (109,90,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8 D9  | P0\nD10 D11 D12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19  | P1\nD20 D21 D22 D23 D24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29  | P2\nD30 D31 D32 D33 D34 D35 D36 D37 D38 D39  | P3\nD40 D41 D42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47 D48 D49  | P4\nD50 D51 D52 D53 D54 D55 D56 D57 D58 D59  | P5\nD60 D61 D62 D63 D64 D65 D66 D67 D68 D69  | P6\nD70 D71 D72 D73 D74 D75 D76 D77 D78 D79  | P7\nD80 D81 D82 D83 D84 D85 D86 D87 D88 D89  | P8\n------------------------------\nP9 P10 P11 P12 P13 P14 P15 P16 P17 P18   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 0 0 0 1 1 1 1 1 1 1\n0 0 1 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0\n1 1 1 1 0 1 0 0 1 1 1\n0 0 1 1 1 0 0 0 0 0 1\n1 0 1 0 0 0 1 1 1 1 0\n0 0 1 1 1 1 0 1 1 1 1\n0 0 1 0 0 1 0 1 0 1 0\n0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 1\n1 1 1 1 0 1 1 1 0 0 1\n0 0 1 0 1 0 1 1 0 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "9",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "74",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (119,99,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8 D9 D10  | P0\nD11 D12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21  | P1\nD22 D23 D24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31 D32  | P2\nD33 D34 D35 D36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41 D42 D43  | P3\nD44 D45 D46 D47 D48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53 D54  | P4\nD55 D56 D57 D58 D59 D60 D61 D62 D63 D64 D65  | P5\nD66 D67 D68 D69 D70 D71 D72 D73 D74 D75 D76  | P6\nD77 D78 D79 D80 D81 D82 D83 D84 D85 D86 D87  | P7\nD88 D89 D90 D91 D92 D93 D94 D95 D96 D97 D98  | P8\n---------------------------------\nP9 P10 P11 P12 P13 P14 P15 P16 P17 P18 P19   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 0 0\n1 0 1 0 1 1 0 1 1 0 0 0\n1 0 0 1 1 0 1 1 0 0 0 1\n1 1 1 1 1 0 0 1 0 1 0 1\n0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 1 0 0\n0 0 0 0 1 1 0 0 0 1 0 1\n1 0 0 1 0 1 0 0 1 0 1 0\n0 0 0 1 1 1 0 0 1 1 0 1\n0 0 0 0 1 1 1 1 0 1 1 0\n1 1 0 0 0 1 0 0 1 0 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 6, column 3. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "9",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "75",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (119,99,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8 D9 D10  | P0\nD11 D12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21  | P1\nD22 D23 D24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31 D32  | P2\nD33 D34 D35 D36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41 D42 D43  | P3\nD44 D45 D46 D47 D48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53 D54  | P4\nD55 D56 D57 D58 D59 D60 D61 D62 D63 D64 D65  | P5\nD66 D67 D68 D69 D70 D71 D72 D73 D74 D75 D76  | P6\nD77 D78 D79 D80 D81 D82 D83 D84 D85 D86 D87  | P7\nD88 D89 D90 D91 D92 D93 D94 D95 D96 D97 D98  | P8\n---------------------------------\nP9 P10 P11 P12 P13 P14 P15 P16 P17 P18 P19   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 0 1 0 1 1 0 1 0 0 0 0\n1 1 1 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 1\n0 0 0 1 1 1 0 1 0 1 0 1\n1 1 1 0 1 0 1 0 0 1 1 1\n1 1 0 1 0 1 0 1 0 1 0 0\n0 0 0 1 1 1 0 1 1 0 1 0\n1 1 1 0 1 1 1 1 0 0 0 1\n1 1 1 1 0 0 1 1 0 1 1 0\n0 0 0 0 1 0 1 0 1 1 0 0\n1 1 1 0 0 1 0 1 1 1 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 1, column 8. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "9",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "76",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (119,99,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8 D9 D10  | P0\nD11 D12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21  | P1\nD22 D23 D24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31 D32  | P2\nD33 D34 D35 D36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41 D42 D43  | P3\nD44 D45 D46 D47 D48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53 D54  | P4\nD55 D56 D57 D58 D59 D60 D61 D62 D63 D64 D65  | P5\nD66 D67 D68 D69 D70 D71 D72 D73 D74 D75 D76  | P6\nD77 D78 D79 D80 D81 D82 D83 D84 D85 D86 D87  | P7\nD88 D89 D90 D91 D92 D93 D94 D95 D96 D97 D98  | P8\n---------------------------------\nP9 P10 P11 P12 P13 P14 P15 P16 P17 P18 P19   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 0 0 0 0 1 1 0 1 1 0 1\n0 0 1 0 1 1 1 1 1 0 1 1\n1 1 1 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0\n0 0 1 0 1 0 0 1 0 0 1 0\n1 0 1 0 0 1 1 0 0 1 1 0\n1 0 1 1 0 1 1 0 0 0 1 0\n1 1 0 0 0 0 1 1 0 0 0 0\n1 1 1 1 1 1 0 0 1 0 0 1\n1 0 0 1 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 1\n1 1 0 1 1 1 0 0 1 0 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "9",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "77",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (120,100,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8 D9  | P0\nD10 D11 D12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19  | P1\nD20 D21 D22 D23 D24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29  | P2\nD30 D31 D32 D33 D34 D35 D36 D37 D38 D39  | P3\nD40 D41 D42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47 D48 D49  | P4\nD50 D51 D52 D53 D54 D55 D56 D57 D58 D59  | P5\nD60 D61 D62 D63 D64 D65 D66 D67 D68 D69  | P6\nD70 D71 D72 D73 D74 D75 D76 D77 D78 D79  | P7\nD80 D81 D82 D83 D84 D85 D86 D87 D88 D89  | P8\nD90 D91 D92 D93 D94 D95 D96 D97 D98 D99  | P9\n------------------------------\nP10 P11 P12 P13 P14 P15 P16 P17 P18 P19   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 0 1 0 1 0 0 1 1 1 1\n1 1 1 0 0 1 1 0 1 0 0\n0 1 1 1 0 1 0 1 1 1 1\n1 1 1 1 1 1 1 0 1 1 1\n0 0 1 1 1 1 1 1 0 0 0\n0 1 0 1 0 0 0 1 1 1 1\n0 1 1 0 0 1 1 0 0 0 0\n1 0 1 0 0 1 0 0 1 1 1\n1 1 0 1 0 0 0 1 1 0 1\n1 0 1 1 1 0 0 0 0 0 0\n1 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 1 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "10",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "78",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (120,100,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8 D9  | P0\nD10 D11 D12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19  | P1\nD20 D21 D22 D23 D24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29  | P2\nD30 D31 D32 D33 D34 D35 D36 D37 D38 D39  | P3\nD40 D41 D42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47 D48 D49  | P4\nD50 D51 D52 D53 D54 D55 D56 D57 D58 D59  | P5\nD60 D61 D62 D63 D64 D65 D66 D67 D68 D69  | P6\nD70 D71 D72 D73 D74 D75 D76 D77 D78 D79  | P7\nD80 D81 D82 D83 D84 D85 D86 D87 D88 D89  | P8\nD90 D91 D92 D93 D94 D95 D96 D97 D98 D99  | P9\n------------------------------\nP10 P11 P12 P13 P14 P15 P16 P17 P18 P19   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 0 1 0 0 0 1 0 0 1 0\n0 0 1 0 1 1 0 0 0 1 0\n1 0 1 0 1 1 1 1 1 1 0\n1 1 1 1 1 0 0 0 0 1 0\n1 0 1 0 1 0 0 0 1 1 1\n1 1 0 1 0 1 1 1 0 1 1\n0 1 1 0 1 1 0 1 0 1 0\n0 1 1 0 0 1 0 1 0 0 0\n1 0 0 0 0 1 1 0 0 0 1\n0 1 1 1 1 0 1 1 1 0 1\n0 1 0 1 0 0 1 1 1 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "10",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "79",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (131,110,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8 D9 D10  | P0\nD11 D12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21  | P1\nD22 D23 D24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31 D32  | P2\nD33 D34 D35 D36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41 D42 D43  | P3\nD44 D45 D46 D47 D48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53 D54  | P4\nD55 D56 D57 D58 D59 D60 D61 D62 D63 D64 D65  | P5\nD66 D67 D68 D69 D70 D71 D72 D73 D74 D75 D76  | P6\nD77 D78 D79 D80 D81 D82 D83 D84 D85 D86 D87  | P7\nD88 D89 D90 D91 D92 D93 D94 D95 D96 D97 D98  | P8\nD99 D100 D101 D102 D103 D104 D105 D106 D107 D108 D109  | P9\n---------------------------------\nP10 P11 P12 P13 P14 P15 P16 P17 P18 P19 P20   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 1 0 1 1 1 0 0 1 0 1 0\n1 1 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 1 0 0\n1 1 1 1 0 0 1 0 1 0 1 1\n0 0 1 1 1 0 1 0 0 1 0 1\n1 0 0 0 1 0 0 1 1 0 0 0\n1 1 1 0 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0\n0 1 1 0 1 1 1 0 1 1 1 0\n1 0 1 0 1 0 1 0 1 0 0 1\n1 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 1 0 0 0\n1 1 0 1 0 1 1 0 0 1 1 1\n1 0 0 0 0 0 1 1 1 0 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 8, column 2. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "10",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "80",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (142,120,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8 D9 D10 D11  | P0\nD12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23  | P1\nD24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31 D32 D33 D34 D35  | P2\nD36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41 D42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47  | P3\nD48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53 D54 D55 D56 D57 D58 D59  | P4\nD60 D61 D62 D63 D64 D65 D66 D67 D68 D69 D70 D71  | P5\nD72 D73 D74 D75 D76 D77 D78 D79 D80 D81 D82 D83  | P6\nD84 D85 D86 D87 D88 D89 D90 D91 D92 D93 D94 D95  | P7\nD96 D97 D98 D99 D100 D101 D102 D103 D104 D105 D106 D107  | P8\nD108 D109 D110 D111 D112 D113 D114 D115 D116 D117 D118 D119  | P9\n------------------------------------\nP10 P11 P12 P13 P14 P15 P16 P17 P18 P19 P20 P21   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 0 0 1 1 0 1 0 1 1 1 0 0\n0 0 1 0 1 1 1 0 0 1 1 0 0\n0 1 0 0 0 1 0 0 1 1 1 0 1\n0 0 1 0 1 0 0 1 1 1 0 1 0\n1 1 1 0 0 1 1 1 1 1 0 0 0\n1 1 0 1 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0\n0 1 1 0 0 0 1 1 1 1 1 0 1\n1 0 1 1 1 0 0 0 1 0 1 0 0\n0 0 0 1 1 0 1 1 0 1 0 0 1\n0 1 0 0 1 1 1 0 1 1 0 1 1\n1 1 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "10",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "81",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (142,120,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8 D9 D10 D11  | P0\nD12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23  | P1\nD24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31 D32 D33 D34 D35  | P2\nD36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41 D42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47  | P3\nD48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53 D54 D55 D56 D57 D58 D59  | P4\nD60 D61 D62 D63 D64 D65 D66 D67 D68 D69 D70 D71  | P5\nD72 D73 D74 D75 D76 D77 D78 D79 D80 D81 D82 D83  | P6\nD84 D85 D86 D87 D88 D89 D90 D91 D92 D93 D94 D95  | P7\nD96 D97 D98 D99 D100 D101 D102 D103 D104 D105 D106 D107  | P8\nD108 D109 D110 D111 D112 D113 D114 D115 D116 D117 D118 D119  | P9\n------------------------------------\nP10 P11 P12 P13 P14 P15 P16 P17 P18 P19 P20 P21   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 1 1 1 1 0 0 0 0 0 1 0 1\n0 0 0 1 1 1 0 1 1 0 1 1 1\n1 0 1 1 0 0 0 0 0 1 1 0 1\n1 0 1 0 1 1 1 1 0 0 0 0 0\n0 0 0 0 1 1 1 1 0 0 1 1 1\n1 1 0 1 0 1 1 0 1 1 0 0 1\n0 1 0 0 0 1 1 0 0 0 1 0 0\n1 1 1 0 0 0 0 0 1 1 1 0 0\n0 1 1 1 0 1 0 0 0 1 0 0 1\n0 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 1 1 0 1\n0 1 1 0 0 1 0 1 1 1 1 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 4, column 3. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "10",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "82",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (155,132,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8 D9 D10 D11  | P0\nD12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23  | P1\nD24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31 D32 D33 D34 D35  | P2\nD36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41 D42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47  | P3\nD48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53 D54 D55 D56 D57 D58 D59  | P4\nD60 D61 D62 D63 D64 D65 D66 D67 D68 D69 D70 D71  | P5\nD72 D73 D74 D75 D76 D77 D78 D79 D80 D81 D82 D83  | P6\nD84 D85 D86 D87 D88 D89 D90 D91 D92 D93 D94 D95  | P7\nD96 D97 D98 D99 D100 D101 D102 D103 D104 D105 D106 D107  | P8\nD108 D109 D110 D111 D112 D113 D114 D115 D116 D117 D118 D119  | P9\nD120 D121 D122 D123 D124 D125 D126 D127 D128 D129 D130 D131  | P10\n------------------------------------\nP11 P12 P13 P14 P15 P16 P17 P18 P19 P20 P21 P22   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 1 0 1 0 1 0 0 1 0 0 1 0\n0 1 0 1 0 0 0 1 0 0 1 1 1\n1 1 1 1 1 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0\n1 1 1 1 0 1 1 0 0 0 0 0 0\n0 1 1 0 0 0 1 1 1 1 1 0 1\n1 1 1 1 0 0 1 1 0 0 0 0 0\n0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 0\n0 0 1 0 1 0 1 1 1 1 1 0 1\n1 1 0 0 1 0 0 1 1 0 1 0 0\n0 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 1 1 0 0 1\n0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 1\n1 1 1 1 0 1 0 0 1 1 0 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "11",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "83",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (142,120,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8 D9 D10 D11  | P0\nD12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23  | P1\nD24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31 D32 D33 D34 D35  | P2\nD36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41 D42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47  | P3\nD48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53 D54 D55 D56 D57 D58 D59  | P4\nD60 D61 D62 D63 D64 D65 D66 D67 D68 D69 D70 D71  | P5\nD72 D73 D74 D75 D76 D77 D78 D79 D80 D81 D82 D83  | P6\nD84 D85 D86 D87 D88 D89 D90 D91 D92 D93 D94 D95  | P7\nD96 D97 D98 D99 D100 D101 D102 D103 D104 D105 D106 D107  | P8\nD108 D109 D110 D111 D112 D113 D114 D115 D116 D117 D118 D119  | P9\n------------------------------------\nP10 P11 P12 P13 P14 P15 P16 P17 P18 P19 P20 P21   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 0 1 1 0 0 0 1 1 0 0 1 1\n1 0 0 1 0 0 1 1 1 1 0 0 1\n1 0 0 1 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 1 0\n1 1 0 1 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0\n1 0 0 1 1 1 0 1 0 1 0 1 1\n0 0 0 1 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0\n0 1 0 0 0 1 1 0 1 0 1 1 0\n1 0 1 0 1 0 0 1 0 0 0 1 1\n0 1 1 1 0 1 0 0 1 1 1 1 0\n0 1 0 0 0 0 1 0 1 0 0 1 0\n0 0 1 1 0 1 1 1 1 1 0 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 1, column 0. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "10",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "84",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (142,120,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8 D9 D10 D11  | P0\nD12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23  | P1\nD24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31 D32 D33 D34 D35  | P2\nD36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41 D42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47  | P3\nD48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53 D54 D55 D56 D57 D58 D59  | P4\nD60 D61 D62 D63 D64 D65 D66 D67 D68 D69 D70 D71  | P5\nD72 D73 D74 D75 D76 D77 D78 D79 D80 D81 D82 D83  | P6\nD84 D85 D86 D87 D88 D89 D90 D91 D92 D93 D94 D95  | P7\nD96 D97 D98 D99 D100 D101 D102 D103 D104 D105 D106 D107  | P8\nD108 D109 D110 D111 D112 D113 D114 D115 D116 D117 D118 D119  | P9\n------------------------------------\nP10 P11 P12 P13 P14 P15 P16 P17 P18 P19 P20 P21   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 1 0 1 0 0 1 1 1 1 0 1 0\n1 0 1 1 0 1 0 1 0 1 1 1 0\n1 0 1 0 1 1 1 0 1 0 1 1 0\n1 0 1 0 0 0 1 1 1 1 0 1 1\n0 0 1 1 1 1 1 0 0 1 1 0 1\n0 0 0 1 0 1 0 0 0 1 1 0 0\n0 1 1 0 1 0 0 1 0 1 0 1 0\n1 0 1 0 1 1 1 1 1 1 0 1 1\n1 1 1 1 1 1 1 1 1 0 0 0 0\n1 0 0 1 1 1 1 0 0 0 1 1 1\n1 1 1 0 0 1 1 0 1 1 1 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 8, column 11. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "10",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "85",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (155,132,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8 D9 D10 D11  | P0\nD12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23  | P1\nD24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31 D32 D33 D34 D35  | P2\nD36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41 D42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47  | P3\nD48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53 D54 D55 D56 D57 D58 D59  | P4\nD60 D61 D62 D63 D64 D65 D66 D67 D68 D69 D70 D71  | P5\nD72 D73 D74 D75 D76 D77 D78 D79 D80 D81 D82 D83  | P6\nD84 D85 D86 D87 D88 D89 D90 D91 D92 D93 D94 D95  | P7\nD96 D97 D98 D99 D100 D101 D102 D103 D104 D105 D106 D107  | P8\nD108 D109 D110 D111 D112 D113 D114 D115 D116 D117 D118 D119  | P9\nD120 D121 D122 D123 D124 D125 D126 D127 D128 D129 D130 D131  | P10\n------------------------------------\nP11 P12 P13 P14 P15 P16 P17 P18 P19 P20 P21 P22   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 0 0 1 1 1 0 0 1 1 0 0 0\n0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 1 0 1 0 1\n1 1 1 1 1 1 0 1 0 0 0 0 1\n0 0 1 0 1 0 1 1 0 1 0 1 0\n1 0 0 1 0 1 0 0 1 1 1 0 0\n0 1 0 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0\n1 0 1 0 0 1 0 1 1 1 0 1 1\n1 0 0 0 1 1 0 1 1 0 0 1 0\n0 0 1 0 1 0 1 1 0 0 1 1 0\n0 1 0 0 0 0 0 1 1 1 0 0 0\n0 0 1 0 1 0 1 0 1 0 0 1 1\n1 1 1 0 0 1 1 1 1 1 1 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "11",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "86",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (142,120,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8 D9 D10 D11  | P0\nD12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23  | P1\nD24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31 D32 D33 D34 D35  | P2\nD36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41 D42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47  | P3\nD48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53 D54 D55 D56 D57 D58 D59  | P4\nD60 D61 D62 D63 D64 D65 D66 D67 D68 D69 D70 D71  | P5\nD72 D73 D74 D75 D76 D77 D78 D79 D80 D81 D82 D83  | P6\nD84 D85 D86 D87 D88 D89 D90 D91 D92 D93 D94 D95  | P7\nD96 D97 D98 D99 D100 D101 D102 D103 D104 D105 D106 D107  | P8\nD108 D109 D110 D111 D112 D113 D114 D115 D116 D117 D118 D119  | P9\n------------------------------------\nP10 P11 P12 P13 P14 P15 P16 P17 P18 P19 P20 P21   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 0 0 1 0 1 1 0 1 1 1 0 1\n0 1 1 1 1 1 0 1 1 0 1 1 1\n0 0 1 1 1 0 1 1 1 1 0 1 0\n0 1 0 0 1 0 0 1 0 1 0 0 0\n1 1 1 0 1 1 0 1 1 0 0 0 1\n0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 0 0\n0 1 1 0 0 1 0 1 1 1 0 1 1\n1 0 0 1 1 1 1 0 1 1 0 1 0\n1 1 1 1 0 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0\n0 1 0 0 1 1 1 1 0 1 0 0 0\n0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 8, column 10. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "10",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "87",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (155,132,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8 D9 D10 D11  | P0\nD12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23  | P1\nD24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31 D32 D33 D34 D35  | P2\nD36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41 D42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47  | P3\nD48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53 D54 D55 D56 D57 D58 D59  | P4\nD60 D61 D62 D63 D64 D65 D66 D67 D68 D69 D70 D71  | P5\nD72 D73 D74 D75 D76 D77 D78 D79 D80 D81 D82 D83  | P6\nD84 D85 D86 D87 D88 D89 D90 D91 D92 D93 D94 D95  | P7\nD96 D97 D98 D99 D100 D101 D102 D103 D104 D105 D106 D107  | P8\nD108 D109 D110 D111 D112 D113 D114 D115 D116 D117 D118 D119  | P9\nD120 D121 D122 D123 D124 D125 D126 D127 D128 D129 D130 D131  | P10\n------------------------------------\nP11 P12 P13 P14 P15 P16 P17 P18 P19 P20 P21 P22   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 0 0 1 0 0 1 1 1 0 0 1 0\n0 0 0 0 1 0 1 0 0 0 1 1 1\n1 0 0 0 1 0 0 1 0 1 0 1 1\n1 0 1 1 1 0 1 1 0 0 0 0 0\n1 1 0 0 0 1 1 0 0 1 0 0 1\n1 1 0 0 0 1 1 0 1 1 1 0 1\n0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 1 0 1 1\n1 0 0 0 1 1 1 0 1 1 0 0 0\n0 1 0 0 1 0 1 1 0 1 1 1 1\n1 0 0 1 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 1 0\n0 0 1 0 0 1 0 1 1 1 0 0 1\n1 1 0 1 1 0 1 1 1 1 1 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 1, column 6. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "11",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "88",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (143,121,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8 D9 D10  | P0\nD11 D12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21  | P1\nD22 D23 D24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31 D32  | P2\nD33 D34 D35 D36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41 D42 D43  | P3\nD44 D45 D46 D47 D48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53 D54  | P4\nD55 D56 D57 D58 D59 D60 D61 D62 D63 D64 D65  | P5\nD66 D67 D68 D69 D70 D71 D72 D73 D74 D75 D76  | P6\nD77 D78 D79 D80 D81 D82 D83 D84 D85 D86 D87  | P7\nD88 D89 D90 D91 D92 D93 D94 D95 D96 D97 D98  | P8\nD99 D100 D101 D102 D103 D104 D105 D106 D107 D108 D109  | P9\nD110 D111 D112 D113 D114 D115 D116 D117 D118 D119 D120  | P10\n---------------------------------\nP11 P12 P13 P14 P15 P16 P17 P18 P19 P20 P21   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 1 0 0 1 1 1 0 1 1 0 0\n0 0 1 0 0 0 0 1 1 1 1 1\n0 0 1 1 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 1\n1 1 1 0 1 0 1 1 1 1 0 0\n1 0 1 1 0 1 1 1 0 1 1 0\n1 0 0 1 0 1 1 0 1 1 0 0\n1 1 1 0 1 1 1 1 0 0 1 0\n0 1 1 0 0 1 0 0 1 1 1 0\n1 1 1 1 1 1 1 1 1 0 0 1\n0 0 1 0 0 0 0 1 1 1 0 0\n0 1 0 0 1 0 1 0 0 1 1 1\n1 0 0 0 1 0 1 1 1 0 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "11",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "89",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (143,121,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8 D9 D10  | P0\nD11 D12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21  | P1\nD22 D23 D24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31 D32  | P2\nD33 D34 D35 D36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41 D42 D43  | P3\nD44 D45 D46 D47 D48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53 D54  | P4\nD55 D56 D57 D58 D59 D60 D61 D62 D63 D64 D65  | P5\nD66 D67 D68 D69 D70 D71 D72 D73 D74 D75 D76  | P6\nD77 D78 D79 D80 D81 D82 D83 D84 D85 D86 D87  | P7\nD88 D89 D90 D91 D92 D93 D94 D95 D96 D97 D98  | P8\nD99 D100 D101 D102 D103 D104 D105 D106 D107 D108 D109  | P9\nD110 D111 D112 D113 D114 D115 D116 D117 D118 D119 D120  | P10\n---------------------------------\nP11 P12 P13 P14 P15 P16 P17 P18 P19 P20 P21   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 1 0 0 1\n1 0 0 0 0 1 1 0 1 0 1 1\n0 1 0 1 1 1 0 0 0 1 0 1\n0 1 0 1 1 1 1 1 1 0 0 1\n1 0 1 0 0 1 1 1 1 0 0 0\n0 0 0 1 0 0 1 1 0 0 1 0\n0 0 1 1 1 1 1 1 1 0 1 0\n0 1 1 0 0 0 1 1 1 0 1 0\n0 0 0 1 1 1 0 1 0 0 1 1\n0 0 0 1 1 0 0 1 0 1 0 1\n0 1 1 0 1 1 1 1 1 1 0 0\n1 0 0 0 1 0 1 0 1 1 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 9, column 5. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "11",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "90",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (155,132,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8 D9 D10 D11  | P0\nD12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23  | P1\nD24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31 D32 D33 D34 D35  | P2\nD36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41 D42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47  | P3\nD48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53 D54 D55 D56 D57 D58 D59  | P4\nD60 D61 D62 D63 D64 D65 D66 D67 D68 D69 D70 D71  | P5\nD72 D73 D74 D75 D76 D77 D78 D79 D80 D81 D82 D83  | P6\nD84 D85 D86 D87 D88 D89 D90 D91 D92 D93 D94 D95  | P7\nD96 D97 D98 D99 D100 D101 D102 D103 D104 D105 D106 D107  | P8\nD108 D109 D110 D111 D112 D113 D114 D115 D116 D117 D118 D119  | P9\nD120 D121 D122 D123 D124 D125 D126 D127 D128 D129 D130 D131  | P10\n------------------------------------\nP11 P12 P13 P14 P15 P16 P17 P18 P19 P20 P21 P22   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 0 1 0 0 0 1 0 1 1 0 1 0\n1 1 0 0 0 1 1 1 1 0 1 1 0\n1 0 1 1 1 0 0 0 0 0 1 1 0\n0 1 0 0 1 0 1 1 0 1 0 1 0\n0 0 1 1 0 1 1 0 1 0 0 0 1\n0 1 0 1 0 0 1 1 0 1 0 0 1\n1 0 0 1 0 0 0 1 0 1 0 1 1\n0 1 0 0 0 0 1 1 0 0 1 0 0\n0 1 1 1 1 0 0 1 0 1 0 0 0\n0 1 1 0 0 0 1 1 0 0 1 1 0\n1 0 1 1 1 1 1 1 1 1 0 1 0\n1 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "11",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "91",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (168,144,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8 D9 D10 D11  | P0\nD12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23  | P1\nD24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31 D32 D33 D34 D35  | P2\nD36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41 D42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47  | P3\nD48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53 D54 D55 D56 D57 D58 D59  | P4\nD60 D61 D62 D63 D64 D65 D66 D67 D68 D69 D70 D71  | P5\nD72 D73 D74 D75 D76 D77 D78 D79 D80 D81 D82 D83  | P6\nD84 D85 D86 D87 D88 D89 D90 D91 D92 D93 D94 D95  | P7\nD96 D97 D98 D99 D100 D101 D102 D103 D104 D105 D106 D107  | P8\nD108 D109 D110 D111 D112 D113 D114 D115 D116 D117 D118 D119  | P9\nD120 D121 D122 D123 D124 D125 D126 D127 D128 D129 D130 D131  | P10\nD132 D133 D134 D135 D136 D137 D138 D139 D140 D141 D142 D143  | P11\n------------------------------------\nP12 P13 P14 P15 P16 P17 P18 P19 P20 P21 P22 P23   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 1 1 0 1 0 1 0 1 1 0 0 0\n1 0 1 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 1\n0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 1 1 1 1 1\n0 0 1 0 0 1 1 0 0 0 0 1 0\n1 0 1 0 0 0 0 1 1 1 1 0 0\n1 1 1 1 1 0 0 0 1 0 1 0 1\n0 0 1 1 1 0 0 1 1 0 1 0 0\n1 0 1 1 1 0 0 1 0 1 1 0 1\n0 1 1 1 0 1 1 0 1 0 0 1 1\n0 0 0 1 1 0 1 1 1 1 1 0 1\n1 0 0 0 0 0 1 1 1 1 0 0 1\n1 0 1 0 1 0 1 1 1 0 1 0 1\n0 1 1 0 1 0 0 0 1 0 1 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nNo errors detected.",
    "length_level": "12",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "92",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (168,144,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8 D9 D10 D11  | P0\nD12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23  | P1\nD24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31 D32 D33 D34 D35  | P2\nD36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41 D42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47  | P3\nD48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53 D54 D55 D56 D57 D58 D59  | P4\nD60 D61 D62 D63 D64 D65 D66 D67 D68 D69 D70 D71  | P5\nD72 D73 D74 D75 D76 D77 D78 D79 D80 D81 D82 D83  | P6\nD84 D85 D86 D87 D88 D89 D90 D91 D92 D93 D94 D95  | P7\nD96 D97 D98 D99 D100 D101 D102 D103 D104 D105 D106 D107  | P8\nD108 D109 D110 D111 D112 D113 D114 D115 D116 D117 D118 D119  | P9\nD120 D121 D122 D123 D124 D125 D126 D127 D128 D129 D130 D131  | P10\nD132 D133 D134 D135 D136 D137 D138 D139 D140 D141 D142 D143  | P11\n------------------------------------\nP12 P13 P14 P15 P16 P17 P18 P19 P20 P21 P22 P23   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 0 1 0 1 0 0 1 1 0 1 0 1\n0 0 0 1 0 0 0 1 0 1 0 1 0\n0 0 1 0 0 0 0 1 1 1 0 1 0\n1 1 1 1 1 0 0 1 0 0 0 1 1\n0 0 1 1 0 1 1 0 0 1 1 1 1\n0 0 0 0 1 1 0 1 1 1 1 1 1\n0 0 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 1 0 1 1\n1 0 0 1 0 1 1 0 0 0 0 0 0\n0 0 1 1 1 0 0 1 0 0 1 0 1\n1 1 0 1 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0\n0 1 1 1 1 0 1 1 1 1 0 0 0\n1 1 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 1 1 1\n0 0 0 1 1 1 0 1 1 0 1 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 2, column 5. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "12",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "93",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (181,156,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8 D9 D10 D11 D12  | P0\nD13 D14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23 D24 D25  | P1\nD26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31 D32 D33 D34 D35 D36 D37 D38  | P2\nD39 D40 D41 D42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47 D48 D49 D50 D51  | P3\nD52 D53 D54 D55 D56 D57 D58 D59 D60 D61 D62 D63 D64  | P4\nD65 D66 D67 D68 D69 D70 D71 D72 D73 D74 D75 D76 D77  | P5\nD78 D79 D80 D81 D82 D83 D84 D85 D86 D87 D88 D89 D90  | P6\nD91 D92 D93 D94 D95 D96 D97 D98 D99 D100 D101 D102 D103  | P7\nD104 D105 D106 D107 D108 D109 D110 D111 D112 D113 D114 D115 D116  | P8\nD117 D118 D119 D120 D121 D122 D123 D124 D125 D126 D127 D128 D129  | P9\nD130 D131 D132 D133 D134 D135 D136 D137 D138 D139 D140 D141 D142  | P10\nD143 D144 D145 D146 D147 D148 D149 D150 D151 D152 D153 D154 D155  | P11\n---------------------------------------\nP12 P13 P14 P15 P16 P17 P18 P19 P20 P21 P22 P23 P24   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 0 0 0 1 1 0 1 1 0 1 0 1 0\n0 1 1 1 0 1 1 1 0 1 0 1 1 1\n0 1 0 1 1 0 1 1 0 0 1 0 0 0\n1 1 0 1 0 1 1 0 1 1 0 1 1 1\n0 0 1 1 0 1 1 0 0 1 0 1 1 1\n0 1 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 1 1 1 0 1\n0 1 1 0 1 1 1 0 0 0 0 1 1 1\n0 1 0 0 1 1 0 1 0 1 1 1 0 1\n0 0 1 0 1 0 1 1 1 1 1 0 1 0\n1 1 1 1 1 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0\n1 1 1 1 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 1 1 0\n0 1 0 1 0 0 1 0 1 0 1 0 0 1\n1 0 0 1 0 1 0 1 0 1 0 1 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 10, column 1. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "12",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "94",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (168,144,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8 D9 D10 D11  | P0\nD12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23  | P1\nD24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31 D32 D33 D34 D35  | P2\nD36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41 D42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47  | P3\nD48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53 D54 D55 D56 D57 D58 D59  | P4\nD60 D61 D62 D63 D64 D65 D66 D67 D68 D69 D70 D71  | P5\nD72 D73 D74 D75 D76 D77 D78 D79 D80 D81 D82 D83  | P6\nD84 D85 D86 D87 D88 D89 D90 D91 D92 D93 D94 D95  | P7\nD96 D97 D98 D99 D100 D101 D102 D103 D104 D105 D106 D107  | P8\nD108 D109 D110 D111 D112 D113 D114 D115 D116 D117 D118 D119  | P9\nD120 D121 D122 D123 D124 D125 D126 D127 D128 D129 D130 D131  | P10\nD132 D133 D134 D135 D136 D137 D138 D139 D140 D141 D142 D143  | P11\n------------------------------------\nP12 P13 P14 P15 P16 P17 P18 P19 P20 P21 P22 P23   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 1 0 0 1 1 0 1 0 0 0 1 0\n1 0 0 1 1 1 1 0 1 1 0 1 1\n1 0 0 1 0 0 0 1 1 1 1 0 0\n0 1 0 1 1 0 1 1 0 0 1 0 0\n0 1 0 0 1 0 0 0 1 1 0 0 0\n1 1 1 1 1 0 0 1 0 0 0 1 1\n0 1 0 0 1 0 1 0 0 0 0 1 0\n0 0 0 0 1 1 0 1 1 1 1 0 0\n0 0 1 1 0 0 0 0 1 0 1 0 0\n1 1 0 1 1 0 1 0 0 1 1 0 1\n0 0 1 0 1 1 0 0 1 1 1 0 0\n1 0 0 1 1 1 0 1 1 0 0 0 0\n0 0 1 1 1 1 0 0 1 0 0 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 1, column 4. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "12",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "95",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (181,156,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8 D9 D10 D11 D12  | P0\nD13 D14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23 D24 D25  | P1\nD26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31 D32 D33 D34 D35 D36 D37 D38  | P2\nD39 D40 D41 D42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47 D48 D49 D50 D51  | P3\nD52 D53 D54 D55 D56 D57 D58 D59 D60 D61 D62 D63 D64  | P4\nD65 D66 D67 D68 D69 D70 D71 D72 D73 D74 D75 D76 D77  | P5\nD78 D79 D80 D81 D82 D83 D84 D85 D86 D87 D88 D89 D90  | P6\nD91 D92 D93 D94 D95 D96 D97 D98 D99 D100 D101 D102 D103  | P7\nD104 D105 D106 D107 D108 D109 D110 D111 D112 D113 D114 D115 D116  | P8\nD117 D118 D119 D120 D121 D122 D123 D124 D125 D126 D127 D128 D129  | P9\nD130 D131 D132 D133 D134 D135 D136 D137 D138 D139 D140 D141 D142  | P10\nD143 D144 D145 D146 D147 D148 D149 D150 D151 D152 D153 D154 D155  | P11\n---------------------------------------\nP12 P13 P14 P15 P16 P17 P18 P19 P20 P21 P22 P23 P24   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 1 0 1 1 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0\n1 0 1 0 0 1 0 1 1 0 1 1 1 0\n0 0 1 0 0 1 1 0 1 1 0 0 0 1\n0 1 1 1 0 1 0 1 1 1 1 1 1 0\n0 1 1 1 0 0 0 1 1 1 1 1 0 0\n1 1 1 0 1 1 1 0 0 0 0 0 1 1\n1 0 1 1 0 0 0 0 1 1 1 1 1 0\n0 1 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 1 0 1 1 1\n1 0 1 1 1 1 0 1 0 1 0 1 0 0\n0 0 0 0 1 1 1 1 1 0 1 0 1 1\n1 0 0 1 0 0 1 0 1 1 1 1 0 1\n0 0 1 0 0 0 1 0 1 0 0 1 0 0\n0 1 0 0 0 0 0 1 1 0 0 0 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 0, column 8. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "12",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "96",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (155,132,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8 D9 D10 D11  | P0\nD12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23  | P1\nD24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31 D32 D33 D34 D35  | P2\nD36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41 D42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47  | P3\nD48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53 D54 D55 D56 D57 D58 D59  | P4\nD60 D61 D62 D63 D64 D65 D66 D67 D68 D69 D70 D71  | P5\nD72 D73 D74 D75 D76 D77 D78 D79 D80 D81 D82 D83  | P6\nD84 D85 D86 D87 D88 D89 D90 D91 D92 D93 D94 D95  | P7\nD96 D97 D98 D99 D100 D101 D102 D103 D104 D105 D106 D107  | P8\nD108 D109 D110 D111 D112 D113 D114 D115 D116 D117 D118 D119  | P9\nD120 D121 D122 D123 D124 D125 D126 D127 D128 D129 D130 D131  | P10\n------------------------------------\nP11 P12 P13 P14 P15 P16 P17 P18 P19 P20 P21 P22   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 0 1 0 1 0 0 1 0 1 1 0 1\n1 1 0 0 1 0 1 0 1 1 0 1 1\n1 0 1 1 1 0 1 0 0 0 1 1 1\n1 0 1 1 1 0 0 0 1 1 0 0 0\n1 0 0 0 1 1 1 1 1 1 0 1 0\n0 1 0 0 1 0 0 0 1 1 1 0 0\n0 1 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 1 1 1 1\n1 0 0 0 1 0 1 1 0 0 1 1 0\n1 1 1 0 0 0 0 1 0 1 1 1 1\n1 1 0 1 0 1 1 1 1 0 0 0 1\n1 1 1 1 1 0 0 0 1 1 1 0 0\n0 0 1 0 1 0 0 1 0 0 1 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 5, column 4. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "11",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "97",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (168,144,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8 D9 D10 D11  | P0\nD12 D13 D14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23  | P1\nD24 D25 D26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31 D32 D33 D34 D35  | P2\nD36 D37 D38 D39 D40 D41 D42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47  | P3\nD48 D49 D50 D51 D52 D53 D54 D55 D56 D57 D58 D59  | P4\nD60 D61 D62 D63 D64 D65 D66 D67 D68 D69 D70 D71  | P5\nD72 D73 D74 D75 D76 D77 D78 D79 D80 D81 D82 D83  | P6\nD84 D85 D86 D87 D88 D89 D90 D91 D92 D93 D94 D95  | P7\nD96 D97 D98 D99 D100 D101 D102 D103 D104 D105 D106 D107  | P8\nD108 D109 D110 D111 D112 D113 D114 D115 D116 D117 D118 D119  | P9\nD120 D121 D122 D123 D124 D125 D126 D127 D128 D129 D130 D131  | P10\nD132 D133 D134 D135 D136 D137 D138 D139 D140 D141 D142 D143  | P11\n------------------------------------\nP12 P13 P14 P15 P16 P17 P18 P19 P20 P21 P22 P23   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 0 0 1 1 1 1 1 1 0 0 1 0\n0 0 0 1 1 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 1\n1 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 0 0 1 0\n1 0 0 1 1 0 0 1 1 1 0 1 1\n0 0 1 1 1 1 1 0 0 0 1 1 1\n0 1 1 0 0 1 0 1 1 0 1 1 1\n1 0 1 1 0 1 1 1 0 1 1 1 1\n0 0 0 1 0 0 1 1 0 0 1 0 0\n1 1 1 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 0 0\n0 1 1 0 1 0 1 0 1 0 1 0 0\n0 1 0 1 1 1 0 1 0 1 1 0 1\n0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 1 1 0 1 0\n1 1 1 1 1 1 1 0 0 1 1 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 8, column 3. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "12",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "98",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (167,143,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8 D9 D10 D11 D12  | P0\nD13 D14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23 D24 D25  | P1\nD26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31 D32 D33 D34 D35 D36 D37 D38  | P2\nD39 D40 D41 D42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47 D48 D49 D50 D51  | P3\nD52 D53 D54 D55 D56 D57 D58 D59 D60 D61 D62 D63 D64  | P4\nD65 D66 D67 D68 D69 D70 D71 D72 D73 D74 D75 D76 D77  | P5\nD78 D79 D80 D81 D82 D83 D84 D85 D86 D87 D88 D89 D90  | P6\nD91 D92 D93 D94 D95 D96 D97 D98 D99 D100 D101 D102 D103  | P7\nD104 D105 D106 D107 D108 D109 D110 D111 D112 D113 D114 D115 D116  | P8\nD117 D118 D119 D120 D121 D122 D123 D124 D125 D126 D127 D128 D129  | P9\nD130 D131 D132 D133 D134 D135 D136 D137 D138 D139 D140 D141 D142  | P10\n---------------------------------------\nP11 P12 P13 P14 P15 P16 P17 P18 P19 P20 P21 P22 P23   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n0 1 1 1 0 1 0 0 1 1 1 1 1 1\n1 1 0 1 1 1 0 0 1 1 0 0 0 1\n1 1 1 0 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 0 1 1\n1 0 0 1 1 0 1 0 0 0 0 1 1 0\n0 0 1 0 1 0 1 1 1 1 1 0 1 0\n1 0 0 0 0 0 1 1 0 1 1 0 0 1\n0 1 0 0 1 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 0 1\n0 1 1 1 0 1 0 1 1 1 0 0 0 1\n0 1 1 0 1 1 1 1 1 0 0 0 1 1\n0 0 0 1 0 0 0 1 1 1 0 1 1 0\n1 0 0 0 1 0 0 1 0 1 0 1 0 1\n1 0 1 1 0 0 1 0 1 1 0 0 0 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 8, column 6. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "11",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "99",
    "question": "Question:\nConsider the following (167,143,d) block code:\n\nD0 D1 D2 D3 D4 D5 D6 D7 D8 D9 D10 D11 D12  | P0\nD13 D14 D15 D16 D17 D18 D19 D20 D21 D22 D23 D24 D25  | P1\nD26 D27 D28 D29 D30 D31 D32 D33 D34 D35 D36 D37 D38  | P2\nD39 D40 D41 D42 D43 D44 D45 D46 D47 D48 D49 D50 D51  | P3\nD52 D53 D54 D55 D56 D57 D58 D59 D60 D61 D62 D63 D64  | P4\nD65 D66 D67 D68 D69 D70 D71 D72 D73 D74 D75 D76 D77  | P5\nD78 D79 D80 D81 D82 D83 D84 D85 D86 D87 D88 D89 D90  | P6\nD91 D92 D93 D94 D95 D96 D97 D98 D99 D100 D101 D102 D103  | P7\nD104 D105 D106 D107 D108 D109 D110 D111 D112 D113 D114 D115 D116  | P8\nD117 D118 D119 D120 D121 D122 D123 D124 D125 D126 D127 D128 D129  | P9\nD130 D131 D132 D133 D134 D135 D136 D137 D138 D139 D140 D141 D142  | P10\n---------------------------------------\nP11 P12 P13 P14 P15 P16 P17 P18 P19 P20 P21 P22 P23   |\n\nNow we receive the following code words:\n1 0 0 0 0 0 0 1 1 1 1 0 0 0\n0 0 0 1 1 0 0 1 0 0 1 1 0 1\n0 0 0 0 1 0 0 0 1 0 0 1 1 0\n0 0 1 1 1 0 0 1 0 1 1 0 1 1\n0 1 1 1 0 1 0 0 1 1 1 1 1 1\n1 0 1 0 1 0 1 0 0 0 0 0 1 1\n0 0 0 1 0 1 0 1 0 0 0 0 1 0\n0 0 0 0 1 0 0 1 0 1 0 0 0 1\n1 0 0 0 1 1 0 0 1 0 0 1 1 0\n1 0 0 1 1 0 0 1 1 0 0 1 1 1\n1 0 1 0 1 0 1 1 1 0 1 0 0 1\n1 1 0 1 0 1 0 1 0 1 1 1 1 0\nAnswer in the format of original code D in format of  [[D0, D1, D2, ...]]. An example is [[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]] if the original D1 to D8 is 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0 respectively",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0]]",
    "needle": "Solution steps:\nError detected at row 0, column 9. Correcting it.",
    "length_level": "11",
    "difficulty_level": "3",
    "rule_id": "28"
  },
  {
    "idx": "100",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 1110 and suppose that the data D is given by 0001100001010.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 3 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[110]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 1110. Its degree is 3 (since len(G)-1 = 3).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 0001100001010. Append 3 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 0001100001010000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 110.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "3"
  },
  {
    "idx": "101",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 1001 and suppose that the data D is given by 0001001110011.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 3 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[101]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 1001. Its degree is 3 (since len(G)-1 = 3).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 0001001110011. Append 3 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 0001001110011000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 101.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "3"
  },
  {
    "idx": "102",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 1110 and suppose that the data D is given by 0001100001101.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 3 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[110]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 1110. Its degree is 3 (since len(G)-1 = 3).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 0001100001101. Append 3 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 0001100001101000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 110.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "3"
  },
  {
    "idx": "103",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 1001 and suppose that the data D is given by 1101010101000.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 3 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[011]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 1001. Its degree is 3 (since len(G)-1 = 3).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 1101010101000. Append 3 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 1101010101000000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 011.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "3"
  },
  {
    "idx": "104",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 1001 and suppose that the data D is given by 0000110111111.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 3 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[110]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 1001. Its degree is 3 (since len(G)-1 = 3).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 0000110111111. Append 3 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 0000110111111000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 110.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "3"
  },
  {
    "idx": "105",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 1110 and suppose that the data D is given by 1101101111100.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 3 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[010]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 1110. Its degree is 3 (since len(G)-1 = 3).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 1101101111100. Append 3 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 1101101111100000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 010.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "3"
  },
  {
    "idx": "106",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 1100 and suppose that the data D is given by 0100111110111.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 3 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[100]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 1100. Its degree is 3 (since len(G)-1 = 3).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 0100111110111. Append 3 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 0100111110111000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 100.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "3"
  },
  {
    "idx": "107",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 1100 and suppose that the data D is given by 1001000101000.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 3 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[000]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 1100. Its degree is 3 (since len(G)-1 = 3).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 1001000101000. Append 3 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 1001000101000000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 000.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "3"
  },
  {
    "idx": "108",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 1000 and suppose that the data D is given by 0011101001101.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 3 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[000]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 1000. Its degree is 3 (since len(G)-1 = 3).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 0011101001101. Append 3 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 0011101001101000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 000.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "3"
  },
  {
    "idx": "109",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 1111 and suppose that the data D is given by 1101101110110.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 3 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[010]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 1111. Its degree is 3 (since len(G)-1 = 3).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 1101101110110. Append 3 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 1101101110110000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 010.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "3"
  },
  {
    "idx": "110",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 11101 and suppose that the data D is given by 111110000011111.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 4 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[0101]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 11101. Its degree is 4 (since len(G)-1 = 4).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 111110000011111. Append 4 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 1111100000111110000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 0101.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "111",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 10111 and suppose that the data D is given by 010110110110110.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 4 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[0001]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 10111. Its degree is 4 (since len(G)-1 = 4).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 010110110110110. Append 4 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 0101101101101100000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 0001.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "112",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 10100 and suppose that the data D is given by 110110011101101.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 4 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[1100]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 10100. Its degree is 4 (since len(G)-1 = 4).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 110110011101101. Append 4 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 1101100111011010000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 1100.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "113",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 11110 and suppose that the data D is given by 100111111100110.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 4 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[1100]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 11110. Its degree is 4 (since len(G)-1 = 4).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 100111111100110. Append 4 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 1001111111001100000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 1100.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "114",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 10110 and suppose that the data D is given by 111110010100011.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 4 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[1010]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 10110. Its degree is 4 (since len(G)-1 = 4).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 111110010100011. Append 4 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 1111100101000110000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 1010.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "115",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 10110 and suppose that the data D is given by 100101010011111.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 4 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[0000]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 10110. Its degree is 4 (since len(G)-1 = 4).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 100101010011111. Append 4 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 1001010100111110000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 0000.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "116",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 11010 and suppose that the data D is given by 101011011111001.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 4 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[0110]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 11010. Its degree is 4 (since len(G)-1 = 4).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 101011011111001. Append 4 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 1010110111110010000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 0110.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "117",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 10110 and suppose that the data D is given by 101001111011110.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 4 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[0100]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 10110. Its degree is 4 (since len(G)-1 = 4).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 101001111011110. Append 4 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 1010011110111100000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 0100.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "118",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 11111 and suppose that the data D is given by 110111110110000.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 4 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[1011]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 11111. Its degree is 4 (since len(G)-1 = 4).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 110111110110000. Append 4 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 1101111101100000000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 1011.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "119",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 10111 and suppose that the data D is given by 110100000010010.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 4 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[0001]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 10111. Its degree is 4 (since len(G)-1 = 4).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 110100000010010. Append 4 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 1101000000100100000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 0001.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "120",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 101101 and suppose that the data D is given by 11010110101000010.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 5 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[00000]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 101101. Its degree is 5 (since len(G)-1 = 5).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 11010110101000010. Append 5 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 1101011010100001000000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\n    - For each bit (from left to right) in the data, if the bit is 1, XOR the next len(G) bits with the generator.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 00000.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "5"
  },
  {
    "idx": "121",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 111001 and suppose that the data D is given by 11100101110011100.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 5 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[00011]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 111001. Its degree is 5 (since len(G)-1 = 5).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 11100101110011100. Append 5 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 1110010111001110000000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\n    - For each bit (from left to right) in the data, if the bit is 1, XOR the next len(G) bits with the generator.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 00011.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "5"
  },
  {
    "idx": "122",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 100101 and suppose that the data D is given by 10111110111110110.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 5 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[01010]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 100101. Its degree is 5 (since len(G)-1 = 5).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 10111110111110110. Append 5 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 1011111011111011000000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\n    - For each bit (from left to right) in the data, if the bit is 1, XOR the next len(G) bits with the generator.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 01010.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "5"
  },
  {
    "idx": "123",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 110000 and suppose that the data D is given by 01000010011101011.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 5 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[00000]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 110000. Its degree is 5 (since len(G)-1 = 5).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 01000010011101011. Append 5 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 0100001001110101100000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\n    - For each bit (from left to right) in the data, if the bit is 1, XOR the next len(G) bits with the generator.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 00000.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "5"
  },
  {
    "idx": "124",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 111111 and suppose that the data D is given by 10111001111111000.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 5 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[10000]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 111111. Its degree is 5 (since len(G)-1 = 5).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 10111001111111000. Append 5 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 1011100111111100000000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\n    - For each bit (from left to right) in the data, if the bit is 1, XOR the next len(G) bits with the generator.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 10000.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "5"
  },
  {
    "idx": "125",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 101111 and suppose that the data D is given by 01011010110101010.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 5 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[00110]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 101111. Its degree is 5 (since len(G)-1 = 5).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 01011010110101010. Append 5 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 0101101011010101000000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\n    - For each bit (from left to right) in the data, if the bit is 1, XOR the next len(G) bits with the generator.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 00110.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "5"
  },
  {
    "idx": "126",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 111101 and suppose that the data D is given by 00011001011110111.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 5 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[01110]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 111101. Its degree is 5 (since len(G)-1 = 5).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 00011001011110111. Append 5 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 0001100101111011100000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\n    - For each bit (from left to right) in the data, if the bit is 1, XOR the next len(G) bits with the generator.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 01110.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "5"
  },
  {
    "idx": "127",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 110011 and suppose that the data D is given by 10110001011011111.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 5 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[01110]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 110011. Its degree is 5 (since len(G)-1 = 5).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 10110001011011111. Append 5 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 1011000101101111100000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\n    - For each bit (from left to right) in the data, if the bit is 1, XOR the next len(G) bits with the generator.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 01110.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "5"
  },
  {
    "idx": "128",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 111010 and suppose that the data D is given by 00110001111100111.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 5 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[10010]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 111010. Its degree is 5 (since len(G)-1 = 5).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 00110001111100111. Append 5 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 0011000111110011100000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\n    - For each bit (from left to right) in the data, if the bit is 1, XOR the next len(G) bits with the generator.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 10010.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "5"
  },
  {
    "idx": "129",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 100100 and suppose that the data D is given by 11000011110110010.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 5 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[01000]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 100100. Its degree is 5 (since len(G)-1 = 5).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 11000011110110010. Append 5 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 1100001111011001000000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\n    - For each bit (from left to right) in the data, if the bit is 1, XOR the next len(G) bits with the generator.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 01000.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "5"
  },
  {
    "idx": "130",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 1100101 and suppose that the data D is given by 0010100001111111101.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 6 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[110100]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 1100101. Its degree is 6 (since len(G)-1 = 6).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 0010100001111111101. Append 6 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 0010100001111111101000000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\n    - For each bit (from left to right) in the data, if the bit is 1, XOR the next len(G) bits with the generator.\n    - Continue the XOR operations until you reach the end of the padded data. The remaining bits form the remainder.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 110100.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "6"
  },
  {
    "idx": "131",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 1101011 and suppose that the data D is given by 0000110000011111111.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 6 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[010000]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 1101011. Its degree is 6 (since len(G)-1 = 6).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 0000110000011111111. Append 6 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 0000110000011111111000000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\n    - For each bit (from left to right) in the data, if the bit is 1, XOR the next len(G) bits with the generator.\n    - Continue the XOR operations until you reach the end of the padded data. The remaining bits form the remainder.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 010000.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "6"
  },
  {
    "idx": "132",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 1111011 and suppose that the data D is given by 0000110000010010000.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 6 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[101011]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 1111011. Its degree is 6 (since len(G)-1 = 6).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 0000110000010010000. Append 6 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 0000110000010010000000000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\n    - For each bit (from left to right) in the data, if the bit is 1, XOR the next len(G) bits with the generator.\n    - Continue the XOR operations until you reach the end of the padded data. The remaining bits form the remainder.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 101011.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "6"
  },
  {
    "idx": "133",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 1110001 and suppose that the data D is given by 1111110010101011111.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 6 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[011000]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 1110001. Its degree is 6 (since len(G)-1 = 6).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 1111110010101011111. Append 6 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 1111110010101011111000000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\n    - For each bit (from left to right) in the data, if the bit is 1, XOR the next len(G) bits with the generator.\n    - Continue the XOR operations until you reach the end of the padded data. The remaining bits form the remainder.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 011000.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "6"
  },
  {
    "idx": "134",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 1110010 and suppose that the data D is given by 0001010010011011110.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 6 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[010110]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 1110010. Its degree is 6 (since len(G)-1 = 6).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 0001010010011011110. Append 6 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 0001010010011011110000000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\n    - For each bit (from left to right) in the data, if the bit is 1, XOR the next len(G) bits with the generator.\n    - Continue the XOR operations until you reach the end of the padded data. The remaining bits form the remainder.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 010110.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "6"
  },
  {
    "idx": "135",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 1000010 and suppose that the data D is given by 0011100100101011000.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 6 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[000110]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 1000010. Its degree is 6 (since len(G)-1 = 6).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 0011100100101011000. Append 6 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 0011100100101011000000000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\n    - For each bit (from left to right) in the data, if the bit is 1, XOR the next len(G) bits with the generator.\n    - Continue the XOR operations until you reach the end of the padded data. The remaining bits form the remainder.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 000110.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "6"
  },
  {
    "idx": "136",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 1111111 and suppose that the data D is given by 1011110001010101100.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 6 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[111111]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 1111111. Its degree is 6 (since len(G)-1 = 6).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 1011110001010101100. Append 6 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 1011110001010101100000000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\n    - For each bit (from left to right) in the data, if the bit is 1, XOR the next len(G) bits with the generator.\n    - Continue the XOR operations until you reach the end of the padded data. The remaining bits form the remainder.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 111111.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "6"
  },
  {
    "idx": "137",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 1001010 and suppose that the data D is given by 1101001011001110010.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 6 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[000010]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 1001010. Its degree is 6 (since len(G)-1 = 6).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 1101001011001110010. Append 6 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 1101001011001110010000000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\n    - For each bit (from left to right) in the data, if the bit is 1, XOR the next len(G) bits with the generator.\n    - Continue the XOR operations until you reach the end of the padded data. The remaining bits form the remainder.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 000010.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "6"
  },
  {
    "idx": "138",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 1001001 and suppose that the data D is given by 1000110101100111101.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 6 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[101000]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 1001001. Its degree is 6 (since len(G)-1 = 6).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 1000110101100111101. Append 6 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 1000110101100111101000000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\n    - For each bit (from left to right) in the data, if the bit is 1, XOR the next len(G) bits with the generator.\n    - Continue the XOR operations until you reach the end of the padded data. The remaining bits form the remainder.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 101000.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "6"
  },
  {
    "idx": "139",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 1000010 and suppose that the data D is given by 1110111111100101001.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 6 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[000010]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 1000010. Its degree is 6 (since len(G)-1 = 6).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 1110111111100101001. Append 6 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 1110111111100101001000000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\n    - For each bit (from left to right) in the data, if the bit is 1, XOR the next len(G) bits with the generator.\n    - Continue the XOR operations until you reach the end of the padded data. The remaining bits form the remainder.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 000010.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "6"
  },
  {
    "idx": "140",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 11110001 and suppose that the data D is given by 001111010000111010100.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 7 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[1010100]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 11110001. Its degree is 7 (since len(G)-1 = 7).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 001111010000111010100. Append 7 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 0011110100001110101000000000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\n    - For each bit (from left to right) in the data, if the bit is 1, XOR the next len(G) bits with the generator.\n    - Continue the XOR operations until you reach the end of the padded data. The remaining bits form the remainder.\n    - The detailed division process involves iteratively shifting the window and performing XOR whenever the leading bit is 1, \n      ensuring that subtraction in GF(2) (i.e., XOR) is carried out correctly over each set of bits.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 1010100.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "7"
  },
  {
    "idx": "141",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 11000100 and suppose that the data D is given by 111000110101001101111.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 7 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[1110000]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 11000100. Its degree is 7 (since len(G)-1 = 7).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 111000110101001101111. Append 7 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 1110001101010011011110000000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\n    - For each bit (from left to right) in the data, if the bit is 1, XOR the next len(G) bits with the generator.\n    - Continue the XOR operations until you reach the end of the padded data. The remaining bits form the remainder.\n    - The detailed division process involves iteratively shifting the window and performing XOR whenever the leading bit is 1, \n      ensuring that subtraction in GF(2) (i.e., XOR) is carried out correctly over each set of bits.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 1110000.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "7"
  },
  {
    "idx": "142",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 11111101 and suppose that the data D is given by 010001100001101000010.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 7 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[0100101]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 11111101. Its degree is 7 (since len(G)-1 = 7).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 010001100001101000010. Append 7 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 0100011000011010000100000000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\n    - For each bit (from left to right) in the data, if the bit is 1, XOR the next len(G) bits with the generator.\n    - Continue the XOR operations until you reach the end of the padded data. The remaining bits form the remainder.\n    - The detailed division process involves iteratively shifting the window and performing XOR whenever the leading bit is 1, \n      ensuring that subtraction in GF(2) (i.e., XOR) is carried out correctly over each set of bits.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 0100101.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "7"
  },
  {
    "idx": "143",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 11110100 and suppose that the data D is given by 001100110000111111001.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 7 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[0001000]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 11110100. Its degree is 7 (since len(G)-1 = 7).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 001100110000111111001. Append 7 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 0011001100001111110010000000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\n    - For each bit (from left to right) in the data, if the bit is 1, XOR the next len(G) bits with the generator.\n    - Continue the XOR operations until you reach the end of the padded data. The remaining bits form the remainder.\n    - The detailed division process involves iteratively shifting the window and performing XOR whenever the leading bit is 1, \n      ensuring that subtraction in GF(2) (i.e., XOR) is carried out correctly over each set of bits.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 0001000.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "7"
  },
  {
    "idx": "144",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 10000111 and suppose that the data D is given by 100010111010000100000.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 7 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[0000111]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 10000111. Its degree is 7 (since len(G)-1 = 7).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 100010111010000100000. Append 7 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 1000101110100001000000000000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\n    - For each bit (from left to right) in the data, if the bit is 1, XOR the next len(G) bits with the generator.\n    - Continue the XOR operations until you reach the end of the padded data. The remaining bits form the remainder.\n    - The detailed division process involves iteratively shifting the window and performing XOR whenever the leading bit is 1, \n      ensuring that subtraction in GF(2) (i.e., XOR) is carried out correctly over each set of bits.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 0000111.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "7"
  },
  {
    "idx": "145",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 10111010 and suppose that the data D is given by 011000111100100001001.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 7 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[0100010]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 10111010. Its degree is 7 (since len(G)-1 = 7).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 011000111100100001001. Append 7 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 0110001111001000010010000000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\n    - For each bit (from left to right) in the data, if the bit is 1, XOR the next len(G) bits with the generator.\n    - Continue the XOR operations until you reach the end of the padded data. The remaining bits form the remainder.\n    - The detailed division process involves iteratively shifting the window and performing XOR whenever the leading bit is 1, \n      ensuring that subtraction in GF(2) (i.e., XOR) is carried out correctly over each set of bits.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 0100010.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "7"
  },
  {
    "idx": "146",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 10010010 and suppose that the data D is given by 000100001010110101110.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 7 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[1100000]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 10010010. Its degree is 7 (since len(G)-1 = 7).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 000100001010110101110. Append 7 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 0001000010101101011100000000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\n    - For each bit (from left to right) in the data, if the bit is 1, XOR the next len(G) bits with the generator.\n    - Continue the XOR operations until you reach the end of the padded data. The remaining bits form the remainder.\n    - The detailed division process involves iteratively shifting the window and performing XOR whenever the leading bit is 1, \n      ensuring that subtraction in GF(2) (i.e., XOR) is carried out correctly over each set of bits.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 1100000.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "7"
  },
  {
    "idx": "147",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 10100100 and suppose that the data D is given by 100100101011110101111.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 7 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[0010000]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 10100100. Its degree is 7 (since len(G)-1 = 7).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 100100101011110101111. Append 7 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 1001001010111101011110000000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\n    - For each bit (from left to right) in the data, if the bit is 1, XOR the next len(G) bits with the generator.\n    - Continue the XOR operations until you reach the end of the padded data. The remaining bits form the remainder.\n    - The detailed division process involves iteratively shifting the window and performing XOR whenever the leading bit is 1, \n      ensuring that subtraction in GF(2) (i.e., XOR) is carried out correctly over each set of bits.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 0010000.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "7"
  },
  {
    "idx": "148",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 11000010 and suppose that the data D is given by 001101101101001010000.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 7 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[1101000]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 11000010. Its degree is 7 (since len(G)-1 = 7).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 001101101101001010000. Append 7 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 0011011011010010100000000000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\n    - For each bit (from left to right) in the data, if the bit is 1, XOR the next len(G) bits with the generator.\n    - Continue the XOR operations until you reach the end of the padded data. The remaining bits form the remainder.\n    - The detailed division process involves iteratively shifting the window and performing XOR whenever the leading bit is 1, \n      ensuring that subtraction in GF(2) (i.e., XOR) is carried out correctly over each set of bits.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 1101000.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "7"
  },
  {
    "idx": "149",
    "question": "Question: Consider the generator G = 11101101 and suppose that the data D is given by 110010110101101100001.\nUsing modulo-2 division (CRC division), compute the remainder R. Remember to append 7 zeros to D before performing the division. Please provide your answer in the format: [[R]].",
    "answer": "[[0101001]]",
    "needle": "Solution:\nStep 1: Identify the generator G = 11101101. Its degree is 7 (since len(G)-1 = 7).\nStep 2: The data D is given by 110010110101101100001. Append 7 zeros to D, obtaining padded data: 1100101101011011000010000000.\nStep 3: Perform modulo-2 long division (using XOR) on the padded data by G.\n    - For each bit (from left to right) in the data, if the bit is 1, XOR the next len(G) bits with the generator.\n    - Continue the XOR operations until you reach the end of the padded data. The remaining bits form the remainder.\n    - The detailed division process involves iteratively shifting the window and performing XOR whenever the leading bit is 1, \n      ensuring that subtraction in GF(2) (i.e., XOR) is carried out correctly over each set of bits.\nStep 4: The computed CRC remainder R is: 0101001.",
    "rule_id": "27",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "7"
  },
  {
    "idx": "150",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (15,11) code with n = 15 and k = 11. The encoded message with possible error is 110010110110000. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[01010110000]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "11"
  },
  {
    "idx": "151",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (7,4) code with n = 7 and k = 4. The encoded message with possible error is 1010010. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[1010]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "152",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (127,120) code with n = 127 and k = 120. The encoded message with possible error is 0110101010101011111000110100000110111011001011101111011100000011010100101110101001000001011110010100101100011111011100111101001. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[110110101011110001101010001011101100101110111101110000001010100101110101001000001011110010100101100011111011100111101001]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "120"
  },
  {
    "idx": "153",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (63,57) code with n = 63 and k = 57. The encoded message with possible error is 000000011011100110110101001111101101011101101011000000000101100. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[000010111001011010100111011101011101101011000000000101100]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "57"
  },
  {
    "idx": "154",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (15,11) code with n = 15 and k = 11. The encoded message with possible error is 001000011110011. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[10001110011]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "11"
  },
  {
    "idx": "155",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (15,11) code with n = 15 and k = 11. The encoded message with possible error is 110110010011111. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[01000011111]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "11"
  },
  {
    "idx": "156",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (7,4) code with n = 7 and k = 4. The encoded message with possible error is 0101111. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[0111]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "157",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (15,11) code with n = 15 and k = 11. The encoded message with possible error is 100001001010100. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[00101010100]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "11"
  },
  {
    "idx": "158",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (63,57) code with n = 63 and k = 57. The encoded message with possible error is 011010011011011001000010101010011111010101001001011100001001111. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[110010110110100001010101001111010101001001011100001001111]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "57"
  },
  {
    "idx": "159",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (31,26) code with n = 31 and k = 26. The encoded message with possible error is 1011111010101111001100010111111. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[11111010111001100010111111]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "26"
  },
  {
    "idx": "160",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (7,4) code with n = 7 and k = 4. The encoded message with possible error is 1010010. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[1010]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "161",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (7,4) code with n = 7 and k = 4. The encoded message with possible error is 1101010. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[0010]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "162",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (31,26) code with n = 31 and k = 26. The encoded message with possible error is 0001101011010001111010001100100. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[01011101000111010001100100]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "26"
  },
  {
    "idx": "163",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (7,4) code with n = 7 and k = 4. The encoded message with possible error is 1010001. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[1101]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "164",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (127,120) code with n = 127 and k = 120. The encoded message with possible error is 1110000100010001001011011001010000110000100100000011100010001000101100010110001010100100011101011111111101111100101100111001010. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[100000010000010110110010100011000010010000001110001000100101100010110001010100100011101011111111101111100101100111001010]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "120"
  },
  {
    "idx": "165",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (7,4) code with n = 7 and k = 4. The encoded message with possible error is 1111011. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[1111]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "166",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (31,26) code with n = 31 and k = 26. The encoded message with possible error is 1110101001000000010000101010001. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[11010100000010000101010001]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "26"
  },
  {
    "idx": "167",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (15,11) code with n = 15 and k = 11. The encoded message with possible error is 010010100100111. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[01110100111]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "11"
  },
  {
    "idx": "168",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (31,26) code with n = 31 and k = 26. The encoded message with possible error is 1101001100001110011111001100011. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[00010000111011111001100011]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "26"
  },
  {
    "idx": "169",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (15,11) code with n = 15 and k = 11. The encoded message with possible error is 000000001100111. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[00001100110]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "11"
  },
  {
    "idx": "170",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (7,4) code with n = 7 and k = 4. The encoded message with possible error is 0101001. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[0001]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "171",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (7,4) code with n = 7 and k = 4. The encoded message with possible error is 1000100. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[0100]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "172",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (127,120) code with n = 127 and k = 120. The encoded message with possible error is 1011111001100111100111101110101100001111110011001000010100001111100000001111010000100111100101100111000100000001001000110101111. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[111101100111001111011101010000111111001100100001010000111100000001111010000100111100101100111000100000001001000110101111]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "120"
  },
  {
    "idx": "173",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (15,11) code with n = 15 and k = 11. The encoded message with possible error is 100011101011001. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[01111011001]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "11"
  },
  {
    "idx": "174",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (31,26) code with n = 31 and k = 26. The encoded message with possible error is 0011001010111000011011101000001. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[10011011100011011101000001]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "26"
  },
  {
    "idx": "175",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (7,4) code with n = 7 and k = 4. The encoded message with possible error is 0111111. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[1111]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "176",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (15,11) code with n = 15 and k = 11. The encoded message with possible error is 100000011000001. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[00001000000]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "11"
  },
  {
    "idx": "177",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (31,26) code with n = 31 and k = 26. The encoded message with possible error is 1000000001110001101100011010010. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[00000111010101100011010010]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "26"
  },
  {
    "idx": "178",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (7,4) code with n = 7 and k = 4. The encoded message with possible error is 0011110. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[1110]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "179",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (7,4) code with n = 7 and k = 4. The encoded message with possible error is 1011001. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[1001]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "180",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (7,4) code with n = 7 and k = 4. The encoded message with possible error is 1100101. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[0101]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "181",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (127,120) code with n = 127 and k = 120. The encoded message with possible error is 0110101011011010101110110001011000011000001001111111011011111100111101101010011001010010100010101000000000000010101000010100000. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[110111011011011101100010110001100000100111111101101111110111101101010011001010010100010101000000000000010101000010100000]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "120"
  },
  {
    "idx": "182",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (7,4) code with n = 7 and k = 4. The encoded message with possible error is 0111111. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[1111]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "183",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (15,11) code with n = 15 and k = 11. The encoded message with possible error is 000101111001011. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[00110001011]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "11"
  },
  {
    "idx": "184",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (31,26) code with n = 31 and k = 26. The encoded message with possible error is 0010010000100101011011010001111. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[10100110010011011010001111]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "26"
  },
  {
    "idx": "185",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (127,120) code with n = 127 and k = 120. The encoded message with possible error is 0011001111110101000000111001011101001001111011101011000011001011001010000110101100111101000001000000111101010011101010001001000. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[100111110100000001110010110100100111101110101100001100101001010000110101100110101000001000000111101010011101010001001000]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "120"
  },
  {
    "idx": "186",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (7,4) code with n = 7 and k = 4. The encoded message with possible error is 1101110. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[0110]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "187",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (15,11) code with n = 15 and k = 11. The encoded message with possible error is 110010000001111. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[01100001111]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "11"
  },
  {
    "idx": "188",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (7,4) code with n = 7 and k = 4. The encoded message with possible error is 1101100. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[0100]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "189",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (63,57) code with n = 63 and k = 57. The encoded message with possible error is 111111000001110000100011111010000011001011111100011111101000101. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[111000001100010001111101000011001011111100011111101000101]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "57"
  },
  {
    "idx": "190",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (7,4) code with n = 7 and k = 4. The encoded message with possible error is 1100001. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[0001]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "191",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (31,26) code with n = 31 and k = 26. The encoded message with possible error is 0001111111000110011111100011101. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[01111100001011111100011101]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "26"
  },
  {
    "idx": "192",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (15,11) code with n = 15 and k = 11. The encoded message with possible error is 000110011011010. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[01000011010]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "11"
  },
  {
    "idx": "193",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (7,4) code with n = 7 and k = 4. The encoded message with possible error is 1101010. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[0010]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "194",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (7,4) code with n = 7 and k = 4. The encoded message with possible error is 1110101. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[1101]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "195",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (7,4) code with n = 7 and k = 4. The encoded message with possible error is 1011110. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[1010]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "196",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (63,57) code with n = 63 and k = 57. The encoded message with possible error is 011011010110011010110100111000011011111001111101011001011101000. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[111001100111011010011100101011111001111101011001011101000]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "57"
  },
  {
    "idx": "197",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (31,26) code with n = 31 and k = 26. The encoded message with possible error is 0000110100101011101100011110000. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[01100010101101100011110000]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "26"
  },
  {
    "idx": "198",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (63,57) code with n = 63 and k = 57. The encoded message with possible error is 001110111000100110001010011101011001011001111111000110010101110. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[110110001001000101001110101001011001111111000110010101110]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "57"
  },
  {
    "idx": "199",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (7,4) code with n = 7 and k = 4. The encoded message with possible error is 0100110. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[0110]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "200",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (31,26) code with n = 31 and k = 26. The encoded message with possible error is 0100010100100110110001110100100. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[00100010011110001110110100]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "26"
  },
  {
    "idx": "201",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (15,11) code with n = 15 and k = 11. The encoded message with possible error is 000000010101001. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[00000101001]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "11"
  },
  {
    "idx": "202",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (63,57) code with n = 63 and k = 57. The encoded message with possible error is 111110100010011110110011000010000111111001011000000111001101010. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[110100100111011001100001000111111001011000000111001101010]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "57"
  },
  {
    "idx": "203",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (7,4) code with n = 7 and k = 4. The encoded message with possible error is 0011101. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[1001]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "204",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (63,57) code with n = 63 and k = 57. The encoded message with possible error is 011011111111111011010110101010011101000011010000001011100001001. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[111111111111101011010101001101000011010000001011100001001]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "57"
  },
  {
    "idx": "205",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (15,11) code with n = 15 and k = 11. The encoded message with possible error is 100110001110111. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[01001110111]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "11"
  },
  {
    "idx": "206",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (7,4) code with n = 7 and k = 4. The encoded message with possible error is 0110010. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[1011]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "207",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (31,26) code with n = 31 and k = 26. The encoded message with possible error is 0011111011111000101101100001000. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[11111111100101101100001000]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "26"
  },
  {
    "idx": "208",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (7,4) code with n = 7 and k = 4. The encoded message with possible error is 0000111. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[0111]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "209",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (15,11) code with n = 15 and k = 11. The encoded message with possible error is 110100010000000. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[00000000001]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "11"
  },
  {
    "idx": "210",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (7,4) code with n = 7 and k = 4. The encoded message with possible error is 0011100. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[1100]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "211",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (15,11) code with n = 15 and k = 11. The encoded message with possible error is 100011110010001. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[01111010001]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "11"
  },
  {
    "idx": "212",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (7,4) code with n = 7 and k = 4. The encoded message with possible error is 1001000. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[0100]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "213",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (31,26) code with n = 31 and k = 26. The encoded message with possible error is 0111110010001011000111010111011. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[11101000111000111010111011]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "26"
  },
  {
    "idx": "214",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (31,26) code with n = 31 and k = 26. The encoded message with possible error is 0111010101011000100101101010101. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[10100101100100101101010101]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "26"
  },
  {
    "idx": "215",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (31,26) code with n = 31 and k = 26. The encoded message with possible error is 1010000110110010100011111111101. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[10001011001100011111111101]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "26"
  },
  {
    "idx": "216",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (7,4) code with n = 7 and k = 4. The encoded message with possible error is 0010010. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[1110]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "217",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (7,4) code with n = 7 and k = 4. The encoded message with possible error is 0001100. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[0100]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "218",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (7,4) code with n = 7 and k = 4. The encoded message with possible error is 1100111. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[0110]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "219",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (15,11) code with n = 15 and k = 11. The encoded message with possible error is 100111101111011. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[01111111011]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "11"
  },
  {
    "idx": "220",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (31,26) code with n = 31 and k = 26. The encoded message with possible error is 0011010001100101101010110100100. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[10100110010101010110100100]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "26"
  },
  {
    "idx": "221",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (7,4) code with n = 7 and k = 4. The encoded message with possible error is 1001000. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[0100]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "222",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (15,11) code with n = 15 and k = 11. The encoded message with possible error is 000001011111101. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[00101111101]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "11"
  },
  {
    "idx": "223",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (15,11) code with n = 15 and k = 11. The encoded message with possible error is 101110001000111. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[11101000111]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "11"
  },
  {
    "idx": "224",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (63,57) code with n = 63 and k = 57. The encoded message with possible error is 111100010000101000011110010011101100110101000101100101110100000. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[100000001010101111001001111100110101000101100101110100000]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "57"
  },
  {
    "idx": "225",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (127,120) code with n = 127 and k = 120. The encoded message with possible error is 0100111010000101011100110000000010111001010010101010110011001110001011101010111110010100111110101100110101111101110011100100000. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[011110000100111001100000001011100101001010101011001100111001011101010111110010100111110101100110101111101110011100100000]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "120"
  },
  {
    "idx": "226",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (127,120) code with n = 127 and k = 120. The encoded message with possible error is 1101110101010011010101011111000000011101010111000100000011010011011110010100010010000111011010111000000100111110000010001110110. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[011001010010101010111110000001110100011100010000001101001011110010100010010000111011010111000000100111110000010001110110]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "120"
  },
  {
    "idx": "227",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (15,11) code with n = 15 and k = 11. The encoded message with possible error is 010001000011111. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[00100011110]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "11"
  },
  {
    "idx": "228",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (15,11) code with n = 15 and k = 11. The encoded message with possible error is 010011111011011. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[01111011011]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "11"
  },
  {
    "idx": "229",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (31,26) code with n = 31 and k = 26. The encoded message with possible error is 0100101111111001110110011011100. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[01011111100110110011011100]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "26"
  },
  {
    "idx": "230",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (31,26) code with n = 31 and k = 26. The encoded message with possible error is 0000111111100010111001110001011. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[01111110001111001110001010]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "26"
  },
  {
    "idx": "231",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (31,26) code with n = 31 and k = 26. The encoded message with possible error is 1100010111001110011101001110100. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[00101100111011101001110100]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "26"
  },
  {
    "idx": "232",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (7,4) code with n = 7 and k = 4. The encoded message with possible error is 0000011. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[0011]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "233",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (63,57) code with n = 63 and k = 57. The encoded message with possible error is 011100101001011001110010110100011011100110100001101000011110010. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[100110010110111001011010101011100110100001101000011110010]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "57"
  },
  {
    "idx": "234",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (7,4) code with n = 7 and k = 4. The encoded message with possible error is 1011001. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[1001]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "235",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (31,26) code with n = 31 and k = 26. The encoded message with possible error is 0110100011100000011001110100000. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[11001110010011001110100000]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "26"
  },
  {
    "idx": "236",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (7,4) code with n = 7 and k = 4. The encoded message with possible error is 0011101. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[1001]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "237",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (7,4) code with n = 7 and k = 4. The encoded message with possible error is 1010010. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[1010]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "238",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (31,26) code with n = 31 and k = 26. The encoded message with possible error is 1101110111011111111010100110101. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[01101101101111010100110101]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "26"
  },
  {
    "idx": "239",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (31,26) code with n = 31 and k = 26. The encoded message with possible error is 0101101101110011101101101110011. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[01010111001101101101110011]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "26"
  },
  {
    "idx": "240",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (7,4) code with n = 7 and k = 4. The encoded message with possible error is 1111010. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[1010]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "241",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (31,26) code with n = 31 and k = 26. The encoded message with possible error is 0010000110100111111100110011111. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[10001010011111100110011111]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "26"
  },
  {
    "idx": "242",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (31,26) code with n = 31 and k = 26. The encoded message with possible error is 1000110011101001011000000000010. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[01101110100011000000000010]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "26"
  },
  {
    "idx": "243",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (7,4) code with n = 7 and k = 4. The encoded message with possible error is 0100010. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[0010]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "244",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (15,11) code with n = 15 and k = 11. The encoded message with possible error is 111110000110101. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[11000110101]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "11"
  },
  {
    "idx": "245",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (15,11) code with n = 15 and k = 11. The encoded message with possible error is 010110010111010. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[01000111010]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "11"
  },
  {
    "idx": "246",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (15,11) code with n = 15 and k = 11. The encoded message with possible error is 001111110001001. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[11110001001]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "11"
  },
  {
    "idx": "247",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (7,4) code with n = 7 and k = 4. The encoded message with possible error is 0011000. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[1001]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "248",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (7,4) code with n = 7 and k = 4. The encoded message with possible error is 1010001. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[1101]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "4"
  },
  {
    "idx": "249",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (127,120) code with n = 127 and k = 120. The encoded message with possible error is 1111110111010001011001001010010101111111000101110110011000011111110110011100010111110010111110011110000111011110001110111110110. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[111011010000110010010100100111111100010111011001100001111110110011100010111110010111110011110000111011110001110111110111]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "120"
  },
  {
    "idx": "250",
    "question": "Consider a Hamming (15,11) code with n = 15 and k = 11. The encoded message with possible error is 110010011000001. Try to decode the message and give the original message in [[]] format.\n\n                    Note: In this Hamming code, the parity bits are located at positions 1, 2, 4, 8, etc. (positions are 1-based indexed).\n\n                    For example, in a Hamming(7,4) code:\n                    - Position 1: parity bit\n                    - Position 2: parity bit\n                    - Position 3: data bit\n                    - Position 4: parity bit\n                    - Position 5: data bit\n                    - Position 6: data bit\n                    - Position 7: data bit\n                    If the received message was 1011001, we would decode it to get the original 4 data bits. Please only answer the original bits in original order, in this example, [[1001]].Now the example ends. Answer the problem step by step with reliable reasoning process, answer the original data bits in the format [[original_bits]].  ",
    "answer": "[[01001000001]]",
    "rule_id": "29",
    "difficulty": "4",
    "length": "11"
  },
  {
    "idx": "251",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=101, G1=110. Received bits from time 1 to 9 are: 00 11 01 01 01 01 10 00 11. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,1,0,1,0,1,1,1,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "9"
  },
  {
    "idx": "252",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=101, G1=110. Received bits from time 1 to 11 are: 11 10 00 00 00 00 00 11 10 11 01. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,1,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "11"
  },
  {
    "idx": "253",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=101, G1=110. Received bits from time 1 to 15 are: 00 00 11 10 11 01 10 11 01 01 01 10 11 01 01. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,0,1,1,0,1,1,0,1,0,1,1,0,1,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "15"
  },
  {
    "idx": "254",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=101, G1=110. Received bits from time 1 to 17 are: 11 01 10 11 10 11 10 11 10 11 01 10 11 10 11 10 11. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,0,0,1,1,0,0,1,1,0,1,1,0,0,1,1,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "17"
  },
  {
    "idx": "255",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=101, G1=110. Received bits from time 1 to 6 are: 00 11 10 11 01 10. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,1,1,0,1,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "6"
  },
  {
    "idx": "256",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=110, G1=101. Received bits from time 1 to 11 are: 11 10 01 00 11 01 00 11 10 10 01. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,0,0,0,1,1,1,0,1,0,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "11"
  },
  {
    "idx": "257",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=110, G1=101. Received bits from time 1 to 12 are: 00 11 10 10 01 00 00 11 10 10 10 01. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,1,0,1,1,1,1,0,1,0,1,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "12"
  },
  {
    "idx": "258",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=110, G1=101. Received bits from time 1 to 16 are: 00 11 10 01 11 10 01 11 01 00 00 11 01 11 01 00. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,1,0,0,1,0,0,1,1,1,1,0,0,1,1,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "16"
  },
  {
    "idx": "259",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=110, G1=101. Received bits from time 1 to 17 are: 11 01 11 01 00 00 11 10 01 00 11 01 11 10 01 00 11. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,1,0,0,0,0,1,0,0,0,1,1,0,1,1,1,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "17"
  },
  {
    "idx": "260",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=110, G1=101. Received bits from time 1 to 5 are: 00 11 10 10 01. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,1,0,1,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "5"
  },
  {
    "idx": "261",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=011, G1=101. Received bits from time 1 to 11 are: 00 01 11 01 11 01 10 10 11 01 11. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,1,1,0,0,1,0,1,1,0,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "11"
  },
  {
    "idx": "262",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=011, G1=101. Received bits from time 1 to 11 are: 00 01 11 01 10 11 00 00 00 01 11. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,1,1,0,1,1,1,1,1,0,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "11"
  },
  {
    "idx": "263",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=011, G1=101. Received bits from time 1 to 16 are: 01 10 11 01 11 00 00 01 11 00 01 10 11 01 11 00. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,0,0,1,1,1,1,0,0,0,1,0,0,1,1,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "16"
  },
  {
    "idx": "264",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=011, G1=101. Received bits from time 1 to 19 are: 01 11 00 01 10 11 01 10 10 10 10 10 11 00 00 00 01 11 01. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,1,1,0,1,1,0,1,0,1,0,1,1,1,1,1,0,0,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "19"
  },
  {
    "idx": "265",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=011, G1=101. Received bits from time 1 to 5 are: 01 10 11 00 01. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,0,0,0,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "5"
  },
  {
    "idx": "266",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=101, G1=011. Received bits from time 1 to 11 are: 10 11 00 10 11 10 11 00 10 01 11. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,1,1,0,0,1,1,1,0,1,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "11"
  },
  {
    "idx": "267",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=101, G1=011. Received bits from time 1 to 12 are: 10 11 10 11 10 01 11 10 01 01 01 11. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,1,0,0,1,0,0,1,0,1,0,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "12"
  },
  {
    "idx": "268",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=101, G1=011. Received bits from time 1 to 17 are: 00 10 11 10 01 01 11 10 11 10 01 11 00 00 10 01 01. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,1,1,0,1,0,0,1,1,0,1,1,1,1,0,1,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "17"
  },
  {
    "idx": "269",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=101, G1=011. Received bits from time 1 to 19 are: 00 00 00 10 01 11 10 11 10 11 00 10 01 01 01 01 11 00 10. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,0,0,1,0,0,1,1,0,0,0,1,0,1,0,1,1,1,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "19"
  },
  {
    "idx": "270",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=101, G1=011. Received bits from time 1 to 7 are: 00 10 11 00 10 01 01. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,1,1,1,0,1,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "7"
  },
  {
    "idx": "271",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=111, G1=101. Received bits from time 1 to 9 are: 00 00 00 00 11 01 01 11 00. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,0,0,0,1,1,0,0,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "9"
  },
  {
    "idx": "272",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=111, G1=101. Received bits from time 1 to 11 are: 00 00 00 11 10 00 01 01 11 00 00. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,0,0,1,0,1,1,0,0,0,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "11"
  },
  {
    "idx": "273",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=111, G1=101. Received bits from time 1 to 17 are: 00 00 11 01 01 11 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 11 10 00. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,0,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,1,0,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "17"
  },
  {
    "idx": "274",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=111, G1=101. Received bits from time 1 to 19 are: 11 10 11 11 10 00 10 11 11 01 01 00 01 01 00 01 01 00 10. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,0,0,1,0,1,0,0,1,1,0,1,1,0,1,1,0,1,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "19"
  },
  {
    "idx": "275",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=111, G1=101. Received bits from time 1 to 7 are: 11 10 11 11 10 11 11. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,0,0,1,0,0,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "7"
  },
  {
    "idx": "276",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=110, G1=111. Received bits from time 1 to 9 are: 00 00 00 00 00 11 00 10 10. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,0,0,0,0,1,1,0,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "9"
  },
  {
    "idx": "277",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=110, G1=111. Received bits from time 1 to 14 are: 11 00 01 01 10 10 11 10 11 10 11 10 00 01. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,1,1,1,0,1,0,1,0,1,0,1,1,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "14"
  },
  {
    "idx": "278",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=110, G1=111. Received bits from time 1 to 14 are: 00 00 11 00 01 10 10 11 01 00 00 11 11 01. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,0,1,1,1,0,1,0,0,0,0,1,0,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "14"
  },
  {
    "idx": "279",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=110, G1=111. Received bits from time 1 to 18 are: 00 00 11 00 01 10 01 00 00 00 11 00 10 01 00 11 00 01. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,0,0,0,1,1,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "18"
  },
  {
    "idx": "280",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=110, G1=111. Received bits from time 1 to 7 are: 00 00 11 11 10 11 01. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,0,1,0,1,0,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "7"
  },
  {
    "idx": "281",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=011, G1=110. Received bits from time 1 to 8 are: 00 00 01 10 00 01 11 11. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,0,1,1,1,0,1,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "8"
  },
  {
    "idx": "282",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=011, G1=110. Received bits from time 1 to 14 are: 01 11 11 10 01 10 00 01 10 00 00 00 00 01. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,0,1,1,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "14"
  },
  {
    "idx": "283",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=011, G1=110. Received bits from time 1 to 17 are: 01 11 11 11 11 11 11 11 10 01 11 11 10 00 00 00 00. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,0,1,0,1,0,1,0,0,1,0,1,1,1,1,1,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "17"
  },
  {
    "idx": "284",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=011, G1=110. Received bits from time 1 to 20 are: 01 11 11 11 10 01 10 01 10 01 11 11 11 10 00 01 10 00 01 10. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,0,1,0,0,1,1,0,0,1,0,1,0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "20"
  },
  {
    "idx": "285",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=011, G1=110. Received bits from time 1 to 6 are: 01 11 11 11 11 10. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,0,1,0,1,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "6"
  },
  {
    "idx": "286",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=100, G1=101. Received bits from time 1 to 10 are: 11 11 10 01 10 11 10 10 10 10. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,1,1,0,1,1,1,1,1,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "10"
  },
  {
    "idx": "287",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=100, G1=101. Received bits from time 1 to 14 are: 00 00 00 00 00 00 11 00 01 00 00 11 11 10. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,0,0,0,0,0,1,0,0,0,0,1,1,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "14"
  },
  {
    "idx": "288",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=100, G1=101. Received bits from time 1 to 17 are: 11 11 01 01 00 00 00 11 11 10 10 01 10 00 01 00 00. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,1,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,0,1,0,0,0,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "17"
  },
  {
    "idx": "289",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=100, G1=101. Received bits from time 1 to 18 are: 00 11 11 10 10 01 10 11 10 01 01 00 00 11 11 01 10 00. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,1,1,1,1,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,1,1,0,1,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "18"
  },
  {
    "idx": "290",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=100, G1=101. Received bits from time 1 to 7 are: 11 11 01 01 11 00 10. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,1,0,0,1,0,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "7"
  },
  {
    "idx": "291",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=101, G1=100. Received bits from time 1 to 10 are: 11 00 01 11 10 01 11 10 01 00. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,0,1,1,0,1,1,0,1,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "10"
  },
  {
    "idx": "292",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=101, G1=100. Received bits from time 1 to 12 are: 11 11 01 10 01 00 10 00 00 11 00 01. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,1,1,0,1,0,0,0,0,1,0,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "12"
  },
  {
    "idx": "293",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=101, G1=100. Received bits from time 1 to 15 are: 00 00 00 11 00 01 11 10 10 11 11 10 10 11 11. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,0,0,1,0,1,1,0,0,1,1,0,0,1,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "15"
  },
  {
    "idx": "294",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=101, G1=100. Received bits from time 1 to 17 are: 00 00 11 00 10 00 00 11 00 10 00 00 00 00 11 00 10. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,0,1,0,0,0,0,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,1,0,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "17"
  },
  {
    "idx": "295",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=101, G1=100. Received bits from time 1 to 6 are: 11 11 10 01 00 10. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,1,0,1,0,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "6"
  },
  {
    "idx": "296",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=111, G1=011. Received bits from time 1 to 9 are: 00 00 10 01 00 11 00 10 11. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,0,1,1,0,0,0,1,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "9"
  },
  {
    "idx": "297",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=111, G1=011. Received bits from time 1 to 14 are: 00 10 01 00 11 00 10 01 10 00 11 00 10 01. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,1,1,0,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,1,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "14"
  },
  {
    "idx": "298",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=111, G1=011. Received bits from time 1 to 16 are: 00 00 10 11 11 10 11 01 11 11 10 11 01 01 00 01. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,0,1,0,0,1,0,1,0,0,1,0,1,1,0,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "16"
  },
  {
    "idx": "299",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=111, G1=011. Received bits from time 1 to 17 are: 10 01 10 10 10 00 11 10 11 01 11 11 10 01 10 00 11. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,1,1,1,1,0,0,1,0,1,0,0,1,1,1,0,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "17"
  },
  {
    "idx": "300",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=111, G1=011. Received bits from time 1 to 7 are: 10 11 11 00 10 01 00. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,0,0,0,1,1,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "7"
  },
  {
    "idx": "301",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=110, G1=011. Received bits from time 1 to 11 are: 10 11 01 00 00 10 11 11 01 10 01. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,0,0,0,0,1,0,1,1,0,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "11"
  },
  {
    "idx": "302",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=110, G1=011. Received bits from time 1 to 12 are: 00 10 11 11 11 01 10 01 00 10 11 11. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,1,0,1,0,0,1,1,1,0,1,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "12"
  },
  {
    "idx": "303",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=110, G1=011. Received bits from time 1 to 16 are: 10 01 10 01 00 00 10 01 10 01 00 10 11 11 11 01. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,1,0,0,0,0,1,1,0,0,0,1,0,1,0,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "16"
  },
  {
    "idx": "304",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=110, G1=011. Received bits from time 1 to 17 are: 00 10 01 10 01 10 01 10 11 11 11 11 01 00 10 11 01. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,1,1,0,0,1,1,0,1,0,1,0,0,0,1,0,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "17"
  },
  {
    "idx": "305",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=110, G1=011. Received bits from time 1 to 8 are: 10 01 00 00 00 00 00 00. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,1,1,1,1,1,1,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "8"
  },
  {
    "idx": "306",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=010, G1=101. Received bits from time 1 to 11 are: 00 01 11 11 00 10 01 00 01 10 01. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,1,1,0,1,0,0,0,1,0,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "11"
  },
  {
    "idx": "307",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=010, G1=101. Received bits from time 1 to 11 are: 01 10 01 00 00 00 00 01 10 00 11. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,0,0,0,0,0,0,1,0,1,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "11"
  },
  {
    "idx": "308",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=010, G1=101. Received bits from time 1 to 14 are: 01 10 01 00 01 11 11 00 10 00 10 01 00 01. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,0,0,0,1,1,0,1,0,1,0,0,0,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "14"
  },
  {
    "idx": "309",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=010, G1=101. Received bits from time 1 to 20 are: 01 11 10 10 10 10 11 00 10 00 10 01 00 01 10 01 00 01 10 01. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,1,1,1,1,1,0,1,0,1,0,0,0,1,0,0,0,1,0,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "20"
  },
  {
    "idx": "310",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=010, G1=101. Received bits from time 1 to 5 are: 00 01 11 11 00. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,1,1,0,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "5"
  },
  {
    "idx": "311",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=001, G1=111. Received bits from time 1 to 8 are: 01 00 10 10 00 11 10 10. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,1,0,1,1,1,0,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "8"
  },
  {
    "idx": "312",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=001, G1=111. Received bits from time 1 to 12 are: 01 01 10 00 10 11 01 01 11 00 01 01. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,0,1,1,0,0,1,0,0,0,1,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "12"
  },
  {
    "idx": "313",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=001, G1=111. Received bits from time 1 to 14 are: 00 00 00 00 01 00 10 11 01 01 10 00 10 10. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,0,0,0,1,1,0,0,1,0,1,1,0,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "14"
  },
  {
    "idx": "314",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=001, G1=111. Received bits from time 1 to 17 are: 00 01 01 11 01 01 11 00 00 01 00 11 11 11 11 11 10. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,1,0,0,1,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,1,1,1,1,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "17"
  },
  {
    "idx": "315",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=001, G1=111. Received bits from time 1 to 8 are: 00 00 00 01 00 10 11 01. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,0,0,1,1,0,0,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "8"
  },
  {
    "idx": "316",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=111, G1=110. Received bits from time 1 to 9 are: 11 11 10 00 11 00 01 01 00. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,0,0,0,1,1,0,1,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "9"
  },
  {
    "idx": "317",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=111, G1=110. Received bits from time 1 to 11 are: 11 11 01 00 01 10 11 00 10 01 01. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,0,1,1,0,0,1,1,1,0,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "11"
  },
  {
    "idx": "318",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=111, G1=110. Received bits from time 1 to 16 are: 11 00 01 10 00 00 00 11 00 01 01 00 01 10 00 11. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,1,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,0,1,1,0,0,0,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "16"
  },
  {
    "idx": "319",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=111, G1=110. Received bits from time 1 to 17 are: 00 11 00 01 10 11 00 01 01 00 01 10 11 11 01 11 10. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,1,1,0,0,1,1,0,1,1,0,0,1,0,1,0,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "17"
  },
  {
    "idx": "320",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=111, G1=110. Received bits from time 1 to 8 are: 00 11 00 01 01 11 10 00. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,1,1,0,1,0,0,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "8"
  },
  {
    "idx": "321",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=100, G1=111. Received bits from time 1 to 8 are: 11 01 01 11 10 11 00 01. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,0,0,1,1,1,0,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "8"
  },
  {
    "idx": "322",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=100, G1=111. Received bits from time 1 to 11 are: 11 10 00 10 01 01 00 11 01 01 00. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,1,0,1,0,0,0,1,0,0,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "11"
  },
  {
    "idx": "323",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=100, G1=111. Received bits from time 1 to 15 are: 11 10 11 11 11 00 10 01 10 01 01 11 10 00 01. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,1,1,1,1,0,1,0,1,0,0,1,1,0,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "15"
  },
  {
    "idx": "324",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=100, G1=111. Received bits from time 1 to 17 are: 11 01 10 10 00 01 00 11 10 00 01 00 00 00 11 01 01. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,0,1,1,0,0,0,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,1,0,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "17"
  },
  {
    "idx": "325",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=100, G1=111. Received bits from time 1 to 5 are: 11 10 00 01 11. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,1,0,0,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "5"
  },
  {
    "idx": "326",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=011, G1=001. Received bits from time 1 to 9 are: 00 10 01 01 01 11 00 10 11. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,1,1,1,0,0,1,0,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "9"
  },
  {
    "idx": "327",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=011, G1=001. Received bits from time 1 to 12 are: 00 10 01 11 10 11 00 00 10 11 10 01. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,1,0,1,0,0,0,1,0,1,1,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "12"
  },
  {
    "idx": "328",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=011, G1=001. Received bits from time 1 to 14 are: 00 00 00 10 01 11 10 11 00 10 01 01 11 00. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,0,1,1,0,1,0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "14"
  },
  {
    "idx": "329",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=011, G1=001. Received bits from time 1 to 19 are: 00 00 00 10 11 10 11 10 11 10 11 00 00 00 00 00 10 01 01. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,0,1,0,1,0,1,0,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,1,1,1,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "19"
  },
  {
    "idx": "330",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=011, G1=001. Received bits from time 1 to 8 are: 00 10 01 01 11 00 10 01. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,1,1,0,0,1,1,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "8"
  },
  {
    "idx": "331",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=101, G1=110. Received bits from time 1 to 8 are: 11 10 00 11 01 01 01 10. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,1,1,0,1,0,1,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "8"
  },
  {
    "idx": "332",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=101, G1=110. Received bits from time 1 to 11 are: 00 00 00 00 00 11 01 01 01 10 00. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,0,0,0,0,1,0,1,0,0,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "11"
  },
  {
    "idx": "333",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=101, G1=110. Received bits from time 1 to 17 are: 11 01 10 11 01 01 01 10 00 11 01 01 10 11 01 01 10. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,0,0,1,0,1,0,0,0,1,0,1,1,0,1,0,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "17"
  },
  {
    "idx": "334",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=101, G1=110. Received bits from time 1 to 19 are: 00 00 11 01 01 01 01 10 00 11 01 10 00 11 01 01 10 00 00. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,0,1,0,1,0,1,1,1,0,1,1,1,0,1,0,0,0,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "19"
  },
  {
    "idx": "335",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=101, G1=110. Received bits from time 1 to 6 are: 11 01 10 11 10 00. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,0,0,1,1,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "6"
  },
  {
    "idx": "336",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=110, G1=101. Received bits from time 1 to 10 are: 11 01 00 11 01 11 10 01 00 00. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,1,1,0,0,1,0,0,0,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "10"
  },
  {
    "idx": "337",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=110, G1=101. Received bits from time 1 to 13 are: 00 00 11 01 00 11 01 00 00 00 00 11 10. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,0,1,1,1,0,0,0,0,0,0,1,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "13"
  },
  {
    "idx": "338",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=110, G1=101. Received bits from time 1 to 16 are: 11 10 01 00 00 00 11 10 10 10 10 10 01 11 10 01. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,0,0,0,0,0,1,0,1,0,1,0,0,1,0,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "16"
  },
  {
    "idx": "339",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=110, G1=101. Received bits from time 1 to 17 are: 00 11 10 10 10 01 11 01 11 01 11 10 10 01 11 01 11. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,1,0,1,0,0,1,1,0,0,1,0,1,1,0,0,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "17"
  },
  {
    "idx": "340",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=110, G1=101. Received bits from time 1 to 8 are: 00 11 01 00 00 11 01 00. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,1,1,1,1,0,0,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "8"
  },
  {
    "idx": "341",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=011, G1=101. Received bits from time 1 to 11 are: 01 11 01 10 10 10 10 11 00 01 11. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,1,0,1,0,1,0,0,0,1,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "11"
  },
  {
    "idx": "342",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=011, G1=101. Received bits from time 1 to 13 are: 00 01 11 00 01 11 01 10 10 10 10 11 00. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,1,1,1,0,0,1,0,1,0,1,1,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "13"
  },
  {
    "idx": "343",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=011, G1=101. Received bits from time 1 to 15 are: 01 11 00 00 00 01 11 01 10 10 10 11 00 00 00. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,1,1,1,1,0,0,1,0,1,0,0,0,0,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "15"
  },
  {
    "idx": "344",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=011, G1=101. Received bits from time 1 to 17 are: 00 01 11 01 11 01 10 11 00 00 01 10 10 10 10 10 11. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,1,1,0,0,1,0,0,0,0,1,0,1,0,1,0,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "17"
  },
  {
    "idx": "345",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=011, G1=101. Received bits from time 1 to 7 are: 00 01 11 00 00 00 01. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,1,1,1,1,1,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "7"
  },
  {
    "idx": "346",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=101, G1=011. Received bits from time 1 to 10 are: 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 00 10 01. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,0,0,0,0,0,0,0,1,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "10"
  },
  {
    "idx": "347",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=101, G1=011. Received bits from time 1 to 13 are: 10 01 11 00 10 01 11 10 01 11 10 01 01. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,0,0,0,1,0,0,1,0,0,1,0,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "13"
  },
  {
    "idx": "348",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=101, G1=011. Received bits from time 1 to 16 are: 00 00 10 11 00 10 01 11 00 00 00 10 01 11 00 10. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[0,0,1,1,1,0,1,1,1,1,1,0,1,1,1,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "16"
  },
  {
    "idx": "349",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=101, G1=011. Received bits from time 1 to 20 are: 10 01 01 01 11 00 10 11 10 11 00 00 10 01 11 10 11 10 11 00. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,0,1,0,0,0,1,1,0,0,0,0,1,0,0,1,1,0,0,0]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "20"
  },
  {
    "idx": "350",
    "question": "Consider a convolutional code with generators G0=101, G1=011. Received bits from time 1 to 5 are: 10 11 10 11 10. Determine the most-likely state sequence and decoded message. Answer in format [[0,1,0,1,1,1,0]] if decoded message is these bits.",
    "answer": "[1,1,0,0,1]",
    "rule_id": "30",
    "difficulty": "5",
    "length": "5"
  },
  {
    "idx": "351",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 4x4 bit matrix:\n1 1 0 0\n1 0 0 0\n1 1 1 1\n0 1 0 0\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "8"
  },
  {
    "idx": "352",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 4x4 bit matrix:\n1 1 1 1\n0 0 0 1\n0 0 1 1\n0 1 0 1\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "8"
  },
  {
    "idx": "353",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 4x4 bit matrix:\n1 1 0 0\n1 0 1 0\n1 0 0 0\n1 1 1 1\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "8"
  },
  {
    "idx": "354",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 4x4 bit matrix:\n0 0 1 0\n1 0 0 1\n0 1 0 1\n0 1 1 1\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "8"
  },
  {
    "idx": "355",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 4x4 bit matrix:\n1 1 0 1\n1 1 0 1\n0 1 0 0\n1 1 0 0\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "8"
  },
  {
    "idx": "356",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 4x4 bit matrix:\n0 0 0 0\n0 0 1 1\n0 1 1 0\n1 1 1 0\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "8"
  },
  {
    "idx": "357",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 4x4 bit matrix:\n1 0 0 0\n1 1 0 0\n0 0 1 1\n0 0 0 1\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "8"
  },
  {
    "idx": "358",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 4x4 bit matrix:\n1 1 0 0\n0 0 0 0\n0 1 0 1\n0 1 0 1\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "8"
  },
  {
    "idx": "359",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 4x4 bit matrix:\n1 1 1 0\n0 1 0 0\n0 0 1 1\n1 0 0 0\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "8"
  },
  {
    "idx": "360",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 4x4 bit matrix:\n1 0 0 1\n0 0 0 0\n0 0 0 1\n1 1 1 1\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "8"
  },
  {
    "idx": "361",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 5x5 bit matrix:\n1 1 1 0 0\n1 1 0 0 0\n0 0 0 0 0\n0 0 0 0 1\n1 0 1 0 1\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "10"
  },
  {
    "idx": "362",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 5x5 bit matrix:\n1 0 1 1 0\n0 0 1 0 0\n1 0 1 1 1\n0 0 0 1 1\n0 1 1 1 1\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "10"
  },
  {
    "idx": "363",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 5x5 bit matrix:\n0 0 0 0 0\n1 1 1 0 1\n1 0 0 1 1\n1 1 1 1 0\n0 0 0 0 1\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "10"
  },
  {
    "idx": "364",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 5x5 bit matrix:\n1 1 1 0 0\n1 1 0 0 0\n1 0 0 0 1\n0 0 0 0 0\n0 0 1 1 1\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "10"
  },
  {
    "idx": "365",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 5x5 bit matrix:\n0 0 1 1 1\n0 0 0 0 0\n1 0 1 0 0\n0 0 1 0 1\n0 0 0 0 1\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "10"
  },
  {
    "idx": "366",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 5x5 bit matrix:\n1 0 0 1 1\n1 0 1 1 0\n1 1 0 1 0\n0 0 0 1 0\n0 0 1 1 1\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "10"
  },
  {
    "idx": "367",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 5x5 bit matrix:\n0 1 1 1 0\n0 0 1 1 0\n0 1 0 1 0\n0 1 1 0 1\n1 0 0 1 1\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "10"
  },
  {
    "idx": "368",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 5x5 bit matrix:\n0 0 0 1 0\n1 1 1 0 1\n0 0 1 1 1\n0 0 0 0 1\n0 0 1 1 0\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "10"
  },
  {
    "idx": "369",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 5x5 bit matrix:\n1 0 1 0 0\n1 1 0 1 0\n1 0 0 0 1\n1 0 0 1 0\n1 1 1 1 0\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "10"
  },
  {
    "idx": "370",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 5x5 bit matrix:\n0 1 0 0 0\n1 0 0 0 0\n0 1 0 1 1\n0 0 1 0 1\n1 0 0 1 0\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "10"
  },
  {
    "idx": "371",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 6x6 bit matrix:\n1 1 0 0 0 0\n0 0 0 0 0 1\n0 1 1 0 1 1\n0 1 1 0 0 0\n0 1 0 1 0 1\n1 0 0 1 0 1\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "12"
  },
  {
    "idx": "372",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 6x6 bit matrix:\n0 0 1 0 0 1\n0 1 0 1 1 0\n0 1 1 1 0 1\n0 0 1 1 0 1\n0 0 0 0 0 0\n1 1 1 1 0 1\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "12"
  },
  {
    "idx": "373",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 6x6 bit matrix:\n0 0 1 0 1 0\n0 0 0 1 0 0\n0 1 0 1 0 1\n1 1 0 0 0 0\n1 0 0 1 0 0\n0 0 1 0 0 1\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "12"
  },
  {
    "idx": "374",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 6x6 bit matrix:\n1 0 0 0 1 1\n1 0 0 0 0 1\n0 0 0 0 0 0\n0 0 1 1 1 1\n0 0 0 1 0 1\n0 0 1 1 1 1\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "12"
  },
  {
    "idx": "375",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 6x6 bit matrix:\n0 0 0 1 1 1\n1 1 1 0 1 0\n0 0 1 0 0 1\n0 1 1 0 0 1\n0 1 0 1 0 1\n0 0 1 0 1 0\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "12"
  },
  {
    "idx": "376",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 6x6 bit matrix:\n1 1 0 0 0 0\n1 1 0 1 0 1\n0 1 0 1 0 1\n1 1 0 0 1 1\n1 0 1 0 1 1\n1 0 1 1 0 0\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "12"
  },
  {
    "idx": "377",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 6x6 bit matrix:\n0 0 0 0 1 0\n1 0 1 0 0 0\n0 0 0 0 0 1\n1 0 1 1 1 1\n1 0 0 1 0 0\n0 1 0 0 1 1\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "12"
  },
  {
    "idx": "378",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 6x6 bit matrix:\n1 1 0 1 0 0\n1 1 0 0 0 1\n1 1 1 0 0 0\n0 0 0 0 0 0\n1 0 0 0 1 1\n1 1 0 0 1 0\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "12"
  },
  {
    "idx": "379",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 6x6 bit matrix:\n1 1 1 0 1 0\n0 0 0 1 0 0\n0 1 1 1 1 1\n1 0 0 1 1 1\n0 0 1 1 0 0\n0 0 1 0 1 1\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "12"
  },
  {
    "idx": "380",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 6x6 bit matrix:\n1 1 1 1 0 1\n1 1 1 1 1 0\n0 0 1 0 1 1\n0 0 1 1 1 1\n1 0 0 1 0 1\n0 1 1 0 0 1\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "12"
  },
  {
    "idx": "381",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 7x7 bit matrix:\n0 1 1 1 1 0 1\n1 0 0 1 0 0 1\n0 1 1 0 1 0 0\n0 0 0 0 0 1 0\n1 1 1 1 0 1 0\n1 1 0 0 1 1 0\n0 1 1 0 1 1 1\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "14"
  },
  {
    "idx": "382",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 7x7 bit matrix:\n0 1 0 0 1 1 0\n0 0 1 1 1 0 1\n1 1 0 0 1 1 1\n0 0 1 0 0 1 0\n1 0 0 1 1 0 1\n0 0 0 0 0 1 1\n1 1 1 0 1 1 0\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "14"
  },
  {
    "idx": "383",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 7x7 bit matrix:\n1 1 1 0 0 1 1\n0 0 1 1 0 1 0\n1 0 0 1 0 1 0\n1 1 0 0 0 1 0\n0 1 1 1 1 0 1\n0 0 1 0 0 1 0\n0 1 1 0 0 0 0\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "14"
  },
  {
    "idx": "384",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 7x7 bit matrix:\n0 0 0 0 0 1 1\n0 1 1 0 0 1 0\n1 1 0 0 1 0 1\n0 1 1 1 1 0 1\n0 1 1 1 1 0 0\n0 1 0 1 1 1 0\n1 1 0 0 1 0 1\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "14"
  },
  {
    "idx": "385",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 7x7 bit matrix:\n1 1 0 0 1 0 1\n1 1 0 1 1 1 1\n1 0 1 1 0 1 1\n1 1 1 0 0 0 1\n0 0 1 0 0 0 0\n0 1 1 0 1 0 1\n1 1 1 0 0 0 0\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "14"
  },
  {
    "idx": "386",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 7x7 bit matrix:\n0 0 1 1 1 0 1\n0 1 0 1 0 0 1\n1 0 1 0 1 1 0\n0 1 1 0 1 0 1\n1 0 0 0 1 1 0\n0 0 0 1 0 0 1\n1 0 1 0 1 0 0\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "14"
  },
  {
    "idx": "387",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 7x7 bit matrix:\n0 0 0 1 1 1 0\n0 0 1 0 0 1 1\n0 0 1 0 0 0 1\n0 1 1 1 0 1 1\n0 0 0 1 1 0 0\n1 1 1 1 0 0 1\n1 0 0 1 1 1 1\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "14"
  },
  {
    "idx": "388",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 7x7 bit matrix:\n0 0 1 1 0 1 1\n0 1 0 1 0 1 1\n1 0 1 1 0 1 1\n1 1 0 1 0 1 0\n1 1 1 1 1 1 1\n1 1 0 1 0 0 1\n1 1 0 1 0 1 1\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "14"
  },
  {
    "idx": "389",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 7x7 bit matrix:\n0 1 0 1 1 1 1\n1 0 0 1 0 0 1\n0 1 0 1 0 1 0\n0 1 1 1 0 0 1\n1 0 0 0 0 0 0\n1 0 0 0 1 0 0\n0 1 1 0 1 1 0\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "14"
  },
  {
    "idx": "390",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 7x7 bit matrix:\n0 0 0 1 0 0 1\n1 0 1 0 0 0 1\n1 1 0 1 0 1 1\n0 0 1 0 0 0 1\n1 0 0 0 1 0 1\n0 0 1 1 0 0 1\n1 0 1 0 1 1 0\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "14"
  },
  {
    "idx": "391",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 8x8 bit matrix:\n1 1 1 1 1 1 0 1\n1 1 1 0 0 0 1 1\n0 0 0 1 1 0 1 1\n1 0 0 0 0 0 0 1\n1 0 1 0 0 1 1 0\n0 0 1 0 0 0 1 0\n0 0 0 0 1 0 1 0\n0 1 1 0 1 1 1 0\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "16"
  },
  {
    "idx": "392",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 8x8 bit matrix:\n0 1 0 1 0 0 1 1\n1 1 1 1 0 0 1 0\n0 1 0 1 1 0 1 0\n1 0 1 0 1 0 0 1\n0 1 0 1 1 0 1 0\n0 0 1 0 1 0 1 1\n0 1 1 1 0 0 1 0\n0 1 0 1 1 1 0 1\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "16"
  },
  {
    "idx": "393",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 8x8 bit matrix:\n1 1 0 1 0 0 0 1\n0 0 0 1 0 0 0 1\n1 1 1 1 0 1 1 0\n0 1 1 1 0 1 0 0\n0 1 0 0 0 0 0 1\n1 1 0 1 0 0 1 1\n1 1 1 1 1 1 0 0\n1 1 1 1 0 0 0 1\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "16"
  },
  {
    "idx": "394",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 8x8 bit matrix:\n0 1 0 0 0 0 1 0\n0 0 0 0 1 1 0 1\n1 1 1 0 1 0 1 0\n0 0 0 1 1 0 0 1\n0 1 1 0 0 0 0 0\n0 1 0 1 0 0 0 0\n0 0 1 1 1 1 1 0\n0 0 0 0 0 0 0 1\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "16"
  },
  {
    "idx": "395",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 8x8 bit matrix:\n1 1 0 0 1 0 1 0\n0 0 1 1 0 0 1 0\n0 0 1 1 0 1 1 1\n0 0 1 1 1 1 1 1\n1 0 0 0 0 0 0 1\n0 0 0 1 0 1 0 1\n0 0 0 1 0 0 1 0\n0 0 1 1 0 0 0 1\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "16"
  },
  {
    "idx": "396",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 8x8 bit matrix:\n1 1 1 1 1 1 1 0\n1 1 0 1 1 1 0 1\n1 1 0 1 1 1 1 1\n1 1 1 0 0 1 1 0\n1 1 1 1 0 0 1 0\n0 0 1 1 0 1 0 1\n1 0 0 0 1 1 1 0\n0 0 0 0 0 0 0 0\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 0]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "16"
  },
  {
    "idx": "397",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 8x8 bit matrix:\n0 0 0 0 1 1 1 0\n1 0 0 0 1 0 0 1\n0 1 0 0 1 0 1 1\n0 0 0 0 1 1 0 0\n0 0 1 1 0 1 0 0\n1 1 0 1 0 0 1 0\n0 0 0 1 1 1 1 1\n1 0 0 0 0 1 1 0\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "16"
  },
  {
    "idx": "398",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 8x8 bit matrix:\n1 1 0 0 0 1 1 0\n1 0 1 1 1 0 0 1\n0 1 1 0 0 0 1 0\n1 1 0 0 0 1 0 1\n0 0 0 0 1 0 0 1\n1 0 0 0 1 1 0 0\n0 1 0 1 0 1 1 1\n1 0 0 1 1 0 1 1\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[0, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "16"
  },
  {
    "idx": "399",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 8x8 bit matrix:\n0 0 0 0 1 1 0 1\n0 0 0 1 1 1 0 1\n0 1 0 0 0 1 0 0\n0 1 1 0 0 0 1 1\n0 1 1 0 0 0 1 0\n1 0 1 0 0 0 1 0\n0 0 1 0 1 0 0 1\n0 1 1 1 1 1 1 1\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 1, 0, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "16"
  },
  {
    "idx": "400",
    "question": "Question:\nGiven the following 8x8 bit matrix:\n1 1 0 1 1 1 0 1\n0 0 1 0 1 0 0 0\n1 1 0 1 1 0 0 1\n1 0 0 1 1 1 1 0\n0 1 1 0 0 0 0 1\n1 0 0 0 1 1 1 1\n1 0 1 1 0 0 1 0\n1 0 0 1 1 1 0 0\nDetermine the parity bits for a two-dimensional even parity scheme and provide your answer in the format: [[(first the row parity bits, then the column parity bits, then the overall parity bit)]].",
    "answer": "[[0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 0, 1, 1, 1, 0, 0, 1, 0, 0]]",
    "rule_id": "26",
    "difficulty": "2",
    "length": "16"
  }
]